This is Zero One Alpha. We have secured the Falcon.
I say again,We have secured the Falcon.
I will count from one to ten.
Within that you'll tell me what I wanna know.
Otherwise the number ten is the last thing you'll hear.
One, two, three ...
four, five, six, seven, eight ...
Grenade. Get Back.
Shit.
Fucking missed it
How did I fucking miss it...
Merlin, I apologise for putting you in this position.
You trained him well.
James, your training is over.
- Welcome to Kingsman, Lancelot.   - Sir
I'll deal with this mess. Personally.
I very much regret that your
husband's bravery can't be publicly celebrated.
- I hope you understand that.   - How can I understand,
if you won't tell me anything?
I didn't even know he was away with his squad.
I'm afraid I can't say more.
I would like to present you with this medal of valor.
If you look closely on the back, there's a number.
And as a more concrete gesture of our gratitude,
we'd like to offer you a...
Let's call it a favor. The nature of it is your choice.
Just tell the operator:"Oxford's, not Brogue's".
And then I'll know it's you.
I do not want your help.
I want my husband back.
- What's your name, young man?   - Eggsy.
Hello, Eggsy. Can I see that?
You take care of this, Eggsy. Alright?
And take care of your mother too.
So sorry, Professor Arnold. Just a tiny bit more.
Oh for god's sakes, just take it off.
I am under very strict instructions not to hurt you.
Look, you've made a mistake.
I am university lecturer. I've got no money.
This isn't about money. Our boss just wants to just talk to you.
Am I meant to find that reassuring?
He'll be here soon. He'll explain.
Do you like whiskey? Red, get a '62 Dalmore.
Honestly, this whiskey is amazing.
You will shit.
I suppose asking to borrow a cup of sugar is a step too far.
Professor Arnold, I'm here to take you home.
1962 Dalmore . It would be a sin to spill any.
Don't you think?
Can you hold these, please?
Thank you.
Everything is clean.
My kind welcome.
No stomach for violence. I mean, literally.
I see one drop of blood, it's me done.
I am like ...projectile.
Listen, I'm so sorry you had to witness all this unpleasantness.
due to our uninvited guest. But I promise you:
By the time I find out who he works for ...
you and I will be the best of friends.
To the shop, please.
Arthur is in the dining room, sir.
- Arthur.   - Galahad.
The others were beginning to
wonder if we were going to have a double toast.
Gentlemen, I am thankful to say that it's been 17 years ...
since we last had occasion to use this decanter.
Lancelot was an outstanding agent and a true Kingsman.
He will be sorely missed. To Lancelot.
To Lancelot.
I intend to start the selection process
for Lancelot's replacement tomorrow.
I want each of you to propose
a candidate and have them report to UK HQ
No later than 9 p.M. GMT. Thank you.
Merlin. Come in.
Lancelot was investigating a group of
mercenaries who were experimenting with biological weaponry.
Glasses, gentlemen. Please.
Uganda, 2012. Synthetic Cathinone.
You put it in the water supply of a guerrilla army base.
Rage, cannibalism. Multiple fatalities.
Chechnya 2013. Insurgents turned on one another.
Indisputable, the work of our mercenaries
but no trace of any chemicals of any kind.
So what happened to Lancelot?
He tracked them to this property in Argentina.
And while he had them under surveillance,
he became aware that they had effected a kidnapping.
So he executed a solo rescue mission...which failed.
This is his last transmission:
- Who is he?   - Some climate change doomsayer.
Expounded something called Gaia
theory about the world healing itself or some such.
But what's curious, is he's not actually missing.
This is Professor Arnold.
At Imperial College, this morning.
It's all yours. And don't forget your membership proposal.
Try picking a more suitable candidate this time.
17 years and still evolving with
the times remains an entirely foreign concept to you.
You don't remind that I
wouldn't be here if it weren't for that young man.
He was as much Kingsman material as any of them. More so.
But he wasn't exactly one of us, was he?
Let's face it, Galahad. Your little experiment failed.
With respect, Arthur, you're a snob.
- With respect?   - The world is changing.
There's a reason why aristocrats developed weak chins.
Eggsy?
Eggsy, come here.
- Got any whistler paper?   - No.
Why don't you do your mamma a favor,
go down to the store and get some.
- Get 'em yourself.   - Oy,
What'd I say to you about speaking to Dean like that?
Feels like a crowd in here Why don't Dean's poodle go?
I'll say you what?
Why don't you take this and
get the stuff and get yourself some sweets?
And while you're gone,
we'll show your mother how three can be a good company.
Thanks babe.
Come here.
Here we go.
Is it better?
If Dean treats mum so bad, why doesn't she leave him?
Low self-esteem. That's her problem.
Fuck off, why would she have low self-esteem?
Note his mum's a wolfie.
- No offense pal.   - It's alright.
One of this days I'm gonna smash his face in.
Are you mental, cuz?
He'll just get that lot to do you
and then pretend he knew nothing...about it.
Oy, you think you can chat shit about us and
we'll do nothing just because our guy's bangin' Eggsy's mum?
- Pretty much, yeah.   - Leave it,
let's just go, man. It's not worth it.
You boys have overstayed your welcome. Leave.
What?
Sorry about that bro.
Yeah...muck.
They are not fucking worth it, cuz.
It's freezing. Why are we walking?
You jacked his fucking car keys, bruh?
Yeah, now we're gonna nick his car.
Shit.
Hold on boys.
That's my fucking car.
Hey! Hey! Eggsy.
I swear, you're in fucking trouble.
You are fucking dead!
Stop it!
I'm gonna fucking kill you.
Floor it, Eggsy.
Hey yeah Dean, look it's me.
Eggsy just stole my fucking car.
I've come out of the pub, he's done 15
about donuts on my fucking face and then he's drove off.
He's disrespecting me and so he's disrespecting you.
Oh hold up. What the...
Damn it.
Foxes are vermin, guys. You should've driven it over.
I should've done a lot of things.
I'll sort this, get out of the car.
Get out of the fucking car.
Eggsy, there is no such thing as honor among thieves.
Now you can start giving
me some names of the boys you were with...
Or you go down. It's up to you.
I want to exercise my right to a phone call.
Well, I hope it's to your mom...
to tell her that you're going to be 18 months late for dinner.
Customer complaints. How may I help you?
My name's Eggsy Unwin. Sorry, Gary Unwin.
And I'm up shit creek, I'm in an urban police station
and my mom said to call this number if ever I needed help...
I'm sorry, sir. Wrong number.
Wait, wait
Oxford's not Brogue's?
Your complaint has been duly noted,
and we hope that we've not lost you as a loyal customer.
What?
but...yep
Yes, I totally understand.
Eggsy.
- Would you like a lift home?   - Who are you?
- The man who got you released.   - That ain't an answer.
A little gratitude would be nice.
My name is Harry Hart. And I gave you that medal.
Your father saved my life.
So before you was a tailor, was you in the army? Like an officer?
Not quite.
So where was you posted, Iraq or something?
Sorry, Eggsy. Classified.
But my dad saved your life, yeah?
The day your father died, I missed something.
And if it weren't for his courage,
my mistake would have cost the lives of every man present.
So I owe him.
Your father was a brave man. A good man.
And having read your files, I'd think
he'd be bitterly disappointed in the choices you've made.
You can't talk to me like that.
Huge IQ, great performance in primary school.
And it all went tits up.
Drugs, petty crime, never had a job.
Do you think there's a lot of jobs going around?
Doesn't explain why you gave up your hobbies.
First prize, regional under tens' gymnastics
Two years in a row.
Your coach had had you pegged as Olympic team material.
Yeah and when you grow up around someone like my stepdad,
you pick up new hobbies pretty quick.
Always someone else's fault.
And who's to blame you for quitting the Marines?
You were halfway through training, doing brilliantly, but you gave up.
Because my mum went mental.
Banging on about losing me as well as dad.
Then we wouldn't be cannon fodder for snobs like you.
Judging people like me from your ivory towers,
with no thought about why we do what we do.
We ain't got much choice, you get me?
And if we was born with the same silver spoon up our arses...
we would do just as well as you, if not better.
What the fuck you doing here? You taking a piss?
Some more examples of young men
who simply need a silver suppository?
No, they are exceptions. Come on.
Nonsense, we haven't finished our drinks.
After you nicked his car, Dean says
you're a free guy I don't give a shit what your mum says.
Listen, boys.
I have had a rather emotional day, so
whatever your beef with Eggsy is and I'm sure its well founded...
I would appreciate it enormously
if you could just leave us in peace ...
until I finish this lovely pint of Guinness.
You should get out of the way,
Granddaddy. Or you'll get hurt a lot.
He ain't joking, you should go.
Excuse me.
If you're looking for another rent boy,
they're on the corner of Smith's Street.
Manners...
maketh...
the man.
Do you know what that means?
Then let me teach you a lesson.
Are we going to stand around here all day,
or are we going to fight?
You fucking dirty. You fucking dirty.
STUN
Amnesia
Sorry about that. Needed to let off a little steam.
Yesterday a friend of mine died.
He knew your father too, actually.
I do apologise, Eggsy.
I should not have done this in front of you.
No. Please. I won't say nothing,
I swear. If there is one thing I can do, it's keep my mouth shut.
You won't tell a soul?
As a fact, I've never crossed anyone out.
- Is that a promise?   - On my life.
Much appreciated, Eggsy.
You're right about the snobs. But there too, there are exceptions.
Best of luck with everything.
In celebrity news, The Richmond Valentine movie
premiered in Hollywood, last night.
The story of the Internet billionaire's rise to power
is expected to be this award season's hot ticket.
One notable absence from the red carpet is Iggy Azalea,
still missing three days after he....
after she failed to appear at her Oakland concert.
No ransom has been demanded.
Eggsy, just go, please. Because he's gonna...
- Please! Don't hurt him.   - Fuck off!   - Don't hurt him!
Get the fuck away! Shut the fuck up.
Who was with you in that fucking pub?
I want to know the name of the geezer you were with.
I was with no one.
- Who was it?   - I don't know what you're fucking on about.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Fucking tell me the name.
I don't know what you're fucking on about.
You listen to me. I want to know who you was
with in that pub. Do you understand?
I want to know his fucking name.
I swear I'll rip you out.
- Tell me!   - I don't know what you're fucking on about.
- Tell me!   - Just tell him, Eggsy!
Fuck off. Fuck off.
I can kill you right now and no one in the world will know this.
But I wouldn't.
I have enough evidence on your activities to have you locked up for the rest of your life.
- Mister Dean Anthony Baker.   - What the fuck?
So I suggest you leave the boy alone.
Or I shall be forced to deliver it to the appropriate authorities.
Eggsy, meet me at the tailor I told you about.
What the fuck's going on here?
Let's see how you fucking make it.
Here's Eggsy.
Come here.
You wanker! I'll have you soon.
I've never met a tailor before.
But I know you ain't one.
Come with me.
Come on in.
What do you see?
Someone who wants to know what the fuck is going on.
I see a young man with potential.
A young man who is loyal.
Who can do as he is asked, and who wants to do something good with his life.
Did you see the film "Trading Places"?
No.
How about "Nikita"? "Pretty Woman"?
Alright.
My point is,
the lack of a silver spoon has set you on a certain path,
but you needn't stay on it.
If you're prepare to adapt and learn, you can transform.
Oh, like in "My Fair Lady"?
You're full of surprises. Yes, like "My Fair Lady".
Only in this case, I am offering you the opportunity to become a Kingsman.
- A tailor?   - A Kingsman agent.
- Like a spy?   - Of sorts.
- Interested?   - You think I've got anything to lose?
Since 1849, Kingsman Tailors have clothed
the world's most powerful individuals.
In 1919, a great number of them
had lost their heirs to World War 1.
That meant a lot of money going uninherited.
And a lot of powerful men with a desire to preserve peace and protect life.
Our founders realized that
they could channel that wealth and influence for a greater good.
And so began our adventure.
An independent international intelligence agency operating at the highest level of discretion.
Without the politics and bureaucracy...
that undermine the integrity of government run spy organizations.
A suit is the modern gentleman's armor.
And the Kingsman agents are the new knights.
- How deep does this fucking thing go?   - Deep enough.
Shit. We're late.
Your father had the same look on his face.
As did I.
Come on.
Galahad. My code name.
- Late again, sir.   - Good Luck.
In you go.
Fall in.
Ladies and gentlemen, my name is Merlin.
You are about to embark on what is probably the most dangerous job interview in the world.
One of you and only one of you will become the next Lancelot.
Can anybody tell me what this is? Yes
- A body bag, sir.   - Correct.
- Charlie, isn't it?   - Yes, sir.
Good. In a moment, you will each collect a body bag.
You will write your name on that bag.
You will write the details of your next of kin. On that bag.
This represents your acknowledgement of the risks that you are about to face...
as well as your agreement to strict confidentiality,
which incidentally if you break...
will result in you and your next of kin being in that bag.
Is that understood?
Excellent. Fall out.
Roxanne. But call me Roxy.
- I am Eggsy.   - Eggy?   - No. Eggsy.
Eggy...and where did they dig you up?
You know we are not allowed to discuss who proposed us.
Then we need to bite his head off.
Charlie's only making conversation, right Charlie?.
- I'm Digby.   - Digby
Eggy, this is Rufus. Rufus, Eggy.
- So Eggy, are you Oxford or Cambridge?   - Neither.
St. Andrews? Durham?
Oh wait, I think we may have met.
Did you serve me at the McDonalds in Winchester Service Station?
No.
It must be St. Andrews.
- Just ignore them.   - Do you need a pen?
- Cheers.   - Amelia, isn't it?
Amelia. Eggsy.
Hi, Eggsy.
- Don't take any notice of those guys.   - That's what I told him.
It's just scare tactics.
Classic army technique. No one's gonna die.
Shame.
Great, so you don't know, the CIA don't know.
Nobody knows who this guy is?
Fine. Seriously, it's fine.
Well, it's not really fine but it's not why I'm here.
Hell man, you know me. Money's not my issue.
I could have retired straight out of MIT,
fucked off to some island and let the business run itself.
Nobody told me to try and save the planet. I wanted to.
Climate change research, lobbying, years of studying, billions of dollars.
And you know why quit?
Because the last time I checked, the planet was still fucked.
Hence, my epiphany.
Money won't solve this.
Those idiots who call themselves politicians, they bury their heads in the sand ...
and stood for nothing but re-election.
So I spent the last two years trying to find a real solution.
And I found it.
Now, If you really want to make the world a better place...
I suggest you open your fucking ears
because I'm about to tell it to you.
Go on, Mr. Valentine. I'm still listening.
As long as you agree to all my terms.
Do not panic. Listen to me. Stay calm.
Fuck.
- U snorkels.   - U snorkels?
- Showerheads.   - Showerheads?
She's right. Go. Fucking go.
And what about pulling the fucking door?
Congratulations on completing your first task.
Charlie, Roxy, well done.
For those who 're still confused
If you get a breathing tube run the U-bend of a toilet,
you have an unlimited air supply.
Simple physics. Worth remembering.
Eggsy, well done for spotting that was a two-way mirror.
I've seen enough of 'em.
Yeah you can all wipe those smirks off your faces.
Because as far as I am concerned, every single one of you has failed.
You all forgot the most important thing:
Teamwork.
So much for classic army technique.
35, 105.
That's it. That's it.
Hello. Can I help you?
Yes, I have a question about anthropogenic force.
Really? Well, it's actually quite fascinating.
My colleague died trying to rescue you.
And I'm sure you saw how well-trained he was.
So I suggest you tell me who kidnapped you
and why they let you go.
I have no idea what you're talking about ...
I can not say, it was ...
Oh for god's sake, I barely touched you. How man are...
Fuck that guy, whoever he is, I'm gonna...
He made me kill Professor Arnold.
Goddamn loved Professor Arnold.
Well the good news is we know the emergency and surveillance systems work.
You know what is not good news?
"My colleague died." That's what he said.
This is an organization and they are all over us.
Whoever you spoke to...
I told you, I am in contact with the KGB, MI6,
Mossad and Beijing.
- They all insist he wasn't one of theirs.   - Beijing.
So freaky how there's no recognizable name for the Chinese Secret Service.
Now that's what you call a secret, right?
You know what?
Fuck it. We need to speed things up. Bring the product release forward.
They are only halfway into production. Speeding it will cost a fortune.
Do I look like I give a fuck? Just get it done..
As some of you would have learned last night:
Teamwork is paramount here at Kingsman.
We are here to enhance your skills, test you to limits.
Which is why you're gonna pick a puppy.
Wherever you go, your dog goes.
You will care for it, you will teach it.
And by the time they are fully trained, so will you be.
Those of you who are still here, that is.
Do you understand? Choose your puppy.
- A poodle?   - What? They are gun dogs.
Oldest working breed. Easy to train.
A pug?
This is still a bulldog, isn't it?
It would get bigger though, wouldn't it?
Shit.
His MRI shows no signs of concussion.
No direct brain trauma at all.
How much longer can he be out?
That's the million-dollar question.
We don't know what he was exposed to in there.
What about Harry's footage?
It didn't stream to his home terminal?
Encrypted and uncrackable.
If and when he comes round,
you might wanna have a word with him about sharing his password.
Is he gonna be alright?
We need to have patience, Eggsy. But there is hope.
If I were you, I'd concentrate on your training. Make it through the test, make him proud.
Come on, J.B. Come on.
I am not gonna be last cause of you.
J.B, I'll shoot you, goddamn.I'll fucking shoot you.
Merlin said we're not allowed to hold you.
Bollocks.
Water.
Come on then.
Eggsy, you forget it.
Oh what's wrong mate, can't take a joke?
Seriously, you'll get turned out and it's just not worth it.
Maybe I don't give a fuck about getting kicked out.
Really? Come on, you player.
Charlie, fuck off.
Yeah, go on, walk away. Dickhead.
Come on, J.B. It's all right.
You have exactly one hour to complete the test. Starting now.
New target. 800 meters.
It's unbelievable. You're still here.
Lingering on like some big steaming shit that just won't flush.
Roger that. Target identified. And how about you shut the fuck up.
Positive discrimination. It isn't worth it.
Like those fucking steak cooks who go down seaways
because their mum's a one-legged lesbian.
You don't know fuck-all about my grades.
Oh forgive me. I'm sure you're highly educated.
Fire when ready.
How's that for positive discrimination?
I wanna thank you both for listening.
And I really, really appreciate your travelling all this way, Your Royal Highness.
And you too, Prime Minister.
I think this is quite brilliant.
It is absolutely brilliant.
You are completely crazy.
Prime Minister, please remain sober-minded.
How can you take it into consideration?
- No! Don't...   - I'm sorry, Your Royal Highness ...
but you got a big role to play...
in getting the Scandinavian region back on track.
You're popular, inspirational and you have the power to galvanize the people.
Now whether you're on board or not...
I am going to have to insist on getting you somewhere I can ensure your safety.
How about you, Prime Minister? You in or out?
Well, I think it's about time that a politician did something that...
- actually made a difference.   - Too true.
Take her away.
- Drink?   - Why not?
Security, help me.
Don't worry. No harm will come to the princess.
Well I'm Republican anyway, so it really doesn't matter.
Release the princess.
Okay, you're done. Not too bad, right?
- I hardly felt a thing.   - Welcome aboard.
The pleasure is all mine.
Ever heard of knocking?
Only when I'm casing a place to rob.
Merlin said you wanted to see me.
Hope J. B.'s training is going as well as yours is.
Sit.
Congratulations on making it to the final six candidates.
Your test results are even better than I could've hoped.
Come in.
Eggsy, I need to have a private conversation. You're dismissed.
Nonsens, let him observe. He'd learn a thing or two.
As you wish. Take a look at this.
"Oh for god's sake, I barely touched you. How man are..."
Fucking hell. That's ring, Harry.
You blew up his head? It's a bit much, isn't it?
Actually, the explosion was caused by an implant in his neck.
Here. Under that scar.
Did my hardware pick up the signal that triggered it?
Fortunately, yes.
Unfortunately, the IP address is traced to it's registered to the Valentine Corporation.
It's not much of a lead. They have millions of employees worldwide.
No, Richmond Valentine is a genius.
Did you not see his announcement today?
No.
We each spend on average $2,000 a year on cellphone and internet usage.
It gives me great pleasure to announce,
those days are over.
As of tomorrow, every man, woman and child can claim
a free SIM card...
compatible with any cellphone, any computer and ...
utilize my communications network for free.
Free calls. Free internet. For everyone.
Forever.
Valentine's assistant has the same implant scar.
I think Mr. Valentine and I shall have a tete-a-tete.
He's having a gala dinner next week.
I'll get you an invitation. You need to be careful though.
Since you were out, hundreds of VIPs have gone missing.
No ransom notes, exactly like Professor Arnold.
Then I suggest you make my alias somebody worth kidnapping.
- You're afraid of heights?   - Yes, it' OK, but I've done it before.
Probably alright if I don't think of it.
Hey, you'll be alright, You're top of the class.
Listen up, the mission is to land in the target
without the radar detecting you.
If I read you on the radar
or you miss the target, you go home.
Is that understood?
Drop zone coming up. 20 seconds.
Here we go.
Eggsy, I really don't think I can do this.
Of course you can't.
Get to the back and I'll show you how.
- Come on.   - Come on
Eggsy, wait. Hang on.
Roxy, just stop fucking about.
Follow me, yeah?
Come on.
Roxy, it's now or never.
Jump.
Good girl, Rox. I'm glad you made it.
Nice
My my, you're all very cheerful. You really think it was gonna be that straightforward?
Any idiot can read a heads-up display.
A Kingsman agent needs to be able to solve problems under pressure.
Like what to do when one of
your group has no parachute.
What? No parachute? Who?
- Fuck. Which one?   - What do we do?
I told you. Aim for the target
coming under the radar.
And I hope not to be
scraping one of you up.
But if I do have to and you're inside the target...
means I'll be very impressed.
Everybody listen, I've got a plan.
Pair up. Grab the closest person to you.
Rufus, come on.
Fuck.
Rufus.
Oh shit. I can't.
Fuck.
Thank god.
Rufus, you wanker.
We are an odd number now. Quick, make a circle.
Fuck. Fine boys. Let's do it.
We'll pull our cords one by one.
When we know who's it, the person on the rigth grabs him.
OK, Eggsy.
Good plan, Eggsy. You have 30 seconds.
Come on now. Hurry up.
Me first.
Fuck.
Me next.
I'll see you on the ground, boys.
Now me.
Fuck.
Roxy, no matter what happens now, I've got you. Alright?
OK, Eggsy.
- You first, okay?   - Yes
Eggsy Roxy
Oh, shit.
shit.
Hold on.
Hugo, Digby, you don't land in the K
then you're not in the K.
Rufus, you opened too soon. You were all over the radar.
All three of you, pack your bags. Go home.
Eggsy, Roxy, congratulations. You have set a new record.
Opening at 300 feet, that's pretty ballsy.
Well done on completing another task. Follow.
Sorry sir, but why the fuck you choose me as the gim?
Am I the expendable candidate?
No no no. You don't talk to me like that.
If you have a complaint, then you can whisper in my ear.
You need to take that jape off your shoulder.
Mr. DeVere. It's a pleasure to meet you.
I am sorry. I seem to have my dates muddles up.
Oh no no. I canceled the gala because of you.
Anybody willing to donate that much deserves a private dinner.
Come in.
Thank you.
Gotta admit, I was really intrigued to meet you.
There are not many billionaires I do not know.
I don't doubt it.
Obviously, I have had my people looking into your affairs
and that's some pretty old money you're from.
How'd your folks make it?
Property, mostly. Property in the markets.
Nothing personal, if that's your concern.
Ah look, I'm just in to find out what kind of person you are.
I'm sure you understand that.
- I most certainly do.   - Hope you're hungry.
- I'm famished.   - Good. Grab a seat.
- I'd have the Big Mac, please.   - Great choice.
But nothing beats two cheeseburgers with secret sauce.
- Tastes great with this '45 Lafite.   - A classic pairing.
May I suggest Twinkies
with 1937 Chateau d'Yquem for pudding?
I like it.
So you want to donate to my foundation?
You are aware that I wind things down in that area, right?
Climate changes affect us all, Mr. Valentine.
And you are one of the few powerful people who seems to share my concerns.
I stepped things down because I wasn't getting anywhere.
Every bit of reasearch kept pointing to the same thing.
The carbon emissions are a red herring,
and we are past the point of no return no matter what remedial actions we take.
You know your shit.
I sometimes envy the blissful ignorance of those less well-versed in their shit.
As Professor Arnold always said:
"Humankind is the only virus cursed
to live with the horrifying knowledge of its host's fragile mortality."
There are not a lot of people who know about him.
Do you like spy movies, Mr. DeVere?
Nowadays, they're all a little serious for my taste.
But the old ones...marvellous.
Give me a farfetched theatrical plot any day.
The old Bond movies. Oh Man.
When I was a kid, that was my dream job.
A gentleman spy.
I always felt the old Bond films were only as good as the villian.
As a child, I rather fancied
a futuristic colorful megalomaniac.
What a shame we both had to grow up.
Bon appetit.
Just give me a couple of days to think over your proposal.
I'll have my people get in touch with yours and it's all good.
Thank you for such a "happy meal".
- Well, you want me to follow him?   - No.
I put a nanotracker gel in the wine.
We'll know his every move for the next 24 hours.
Finally find out who he works for.
Valentine didn't let me out of his sight.
All I got was this, on the way in.
South Glade Mission Church is a hate group based in Kentucky.
The FBI have been monitoring them for years.
Do you think Valentine is a supporter?
No, I didn't see evidence yet of a direct connection,
but I'll keep looking.
Oh, by the way, the ever-growing list of missing persons...
Now includes Scandinavian Royalty.
Royal Crown Princess Tilde.
Just let me out, you PSYCHO!
I told you, you're free to go anytime you want.
- As long as you agree to my conditions.   - I don't agree.
And I am never ever going to agree!
I see it.
Bitch.
We want to see the British Council.
The list of missing celebrities and dignataries has continued to grow in recent weeks.
And world leaders are coming under increasing pressure to provide answers.
We are doing everything in our power to find princess Tilde.
You know, governments and security forces worldwide are working together...
to find the person behind these abductions.
In other news, people all over the world
continue to wait in line day and night to get their free SIM card.
Mrs. P. You get one?
Yeah, I've been queueing up all day.
This unprecedented giveaway by the philanthropist Richmond Valentine ...
has already seen over a billion cards distributed.
At ease.
So you thought you were done for the day, huh?
Probably not.
- A party?   - Tonight. In London.
- Who is this?   - Your target.
Your mission is to use your NLP Training
to win over the individual in the photograph in your envelope .
And when I say "win over", I do mean in the Biblical sense.
Easy
- Most girls love a bit rough.   - We'll see about that, yeah.
We certainly will.
Hi. Sorry, I just had to come over
and say "Amazing eyes".
- You wearing color contacts?   - No.
- You so are   - Oh my god. 'Nagging'. That's hilarious.
I haven't had anyone try that since the 90s.
Excuse me?
"Negging". Saying something negative
to a pretty girl in order to undermine her social value.
Its supposed to make you want to win his approval.
Absurdly basic neurolinguistic programming technique.
Is it just me or does this champagne taste a l'il bit funny?
That's an acquired taste, mate.
I think it's just cheap.
Get one of these instead. They're delicious.
You know, if you're interested in ornamental techniques,
this guy is textbook.
See what he just did? Its called an 'opinion opener.
He got you talking with a neutral question ...
got all of us involved in the conversation,
so that you crave individual attention.
Nah, I'm just saying that the champagne tastes weird...
Lady Sophie, Montague Herring,
phone call for you at reception.
- Be right back.   - See you in a bit, yeah.
See you in a bit.
Good job, Rox. I'm feeling a bit rough.
You alright?
Sorry to eavesdrop ...
but there is a much easier way to guarantee getting someone home.
Rohypnol.
Or even something stronger.
Who the fuck are you?
Where am I?
This knife can save your life.
Fuck
My employer's two questions for you, Eggsy.
What the fuck is Kingsman? And who is Harry Hart?
I do not know what the fuck that is.
Oh Eggsy, I just killed two of your friends
because they gave me the same bullshit answer.
Just cut the fucking ropes, please.
Hey, Eggsy, is the Kingsman worth dying for?
Fuck you.
Congratulations. Bloody well done.
- How'd the others do?   - Roxy passed with flying colors.
Charlie's up next. Want to watch?
Yeah, alright.
Is Kingsman really worth dying for?
No, it fucking isn't, shit! I'll tell all you want, please.
Chester King's Arthur,
head of a spy agency,
it's called Kingsman. Get me out of here.
Thank you Charlie. Much appreciated.
No, how was the fucking deal
No
I had such high hopes for you. You are a bloody disgrace.
I'm so sorry. Please untie me.
Untie yourself.
Arthur,Arthur, please.
You know who my dad is? Shit!
Anyone? Hello!
Galahad, Percival. Congratulations.
You candidates have reached
the final stage of the testing process.
As tradition allows, you now have 24 hours to spend with them.
Eggsy, you should know your father reached this point.
From now on, there are no safety nets. Understood?
Good. Dismissed.
Charlie, time to go home.
Fuck you.
My fucking dad's gonna hear about this.
"To pee or not to pee?"
That was the headline the
day after I diffused a dirty bomb in Paris.
"Germany 1-England 5."
I missed that game.
I was breaking up an undercover spying at Pentagon.
My first mission. I foiled
the assassination of Margaret Thatcher.
Not everybody had thanked you for that one.
The point is, Eggsy, nobody thanked me for any of them.
Front page news, and all these occasions were celebrity nonsense.
Because it is the nature of
Kingsman that our acheivements remain secret.
A gentleman's name should
appear in the newspaper only three times:
When he's born, when he marries and when he dies.
And we are, first and foremost, gentlemen.
Pretty fucked then.
It's like Charlie said, I am just a pleb.
Nonsense. Being a gentleman has nothing
to do with the circumstances of one's birth.
Being a gentleman is something one learns.
Yeah, but how?
Alright, first lesson,
you should have asked me before you took a seat.
Second lesson, how to make a proper martini.
Yes, Harry.
Goddamn it. It fucking hurts.
You are the one who asked for a biometric
security system. What's wrong with a simple switch?
A simple switch? This is an extremely dangerous machine.
It should only be operated by someone responsible and sane as me.
Bad shit can happen if it falls into the wrong hands.
Are we done here? Shit
No, now this one, for the test of the church.
This one just has a short range. A simple switch will do.
So you gonna teach me how to talk proper like in 'My Fair Lady'?
That'd be absurd. Being a
gentleman has nothing to do with one's accent.
It's about being at ease in one's own skin.
As Hemingway said:"There is
nothing noble in being superior to your fellow man."
"True nobility is being superior to your former self. "
Now, the first thing every gentleman needs is a good suit.
By which I mean a bespoke suit. Never off the peg.
And Kingsman suits are always bulletproof,
So let's get you measured.
And whether you get the job or not, you will
have a lasting and useful memento of your time at Kingsman.
I'm so sorry, sir, but a gentleman is completing his fitting.
- Fitting Room 2 is available.   - One does not use Fitting Room 2...
when one is popping one's cherry.
Perhaps I'll show you Fitting Room 3, while we wait.
- So we going up or down?   - Neither.
Is this it?
Of course not. Pull the hook on your left.
Oh yes Very very nice.
You're going to need a pair of shoes to go with your suit.
An Oxford is any formal shoe, with open lacing.
This additional decorative piece is called broguing.
- "Oxford's, not brogue's."   - Words to live by,
Eggsy. Words to live by.
Try a pair.
Your weapon scores are excellent, by the way.
These you're familiar with.
And this is our standard issue pistol.
It's quite unique. As you all see it, it also
fires a shotgun cartridge for use in messy close-range situations.
- How do they feel?   - Yeah good
Now do your very best in personation of a German aristocrat's formal greeting.
No, Eggsy.
That is sick.
In the old days, they had a phone in the heel as well.
How do I get it back in?
It is coated with one of the
fastest-acting neurotoxins known to man, so very carefully.
Now, I had a lot of fun with this.
One of our finest examples of chemical engineering.
Poison. Harmless when ingested.
But at a time, convenient to you...
it can be remotely activated.
Primed.
Lethal.
And what about these? What do these do? Electrocute you?
- Don't be ridiculous. It's a hand grenade.   - Shut up...
If you want to electrocute someone, you'll need a signet ring.
A gentleman traditionally wears the signet on his left hand,
but a Kingsman wears it on whatever hand happens to be dominant.
If you touch the contact behind the ring,
it delivers 50,000 volts.
And what about them? What makes them so special?
Nothing. That technology is caught up with the spy world.
Put it back, Eggsy.
Perfect timing. Gentleman's just finished.
Mr. DeVere.
What a coincidence. You're totally the reason I'm here.
When you left my house, I was
searching for that dope-ass smoking jacket you had on.
And since I'm going to Royal Ascot,
apparently I need one of these penguin suits ...
Here I am. What are you doing here?
What's up man? Richmond Valentine.
This is my new valet. I was just introducing him to my tailor.
Another coincidence. So am I.
Did you have any chance to
- think further on my proposal?   - Most definitely.
My people will be getting
in touch with you very soon. I guarantee it.
A word of advice: Ascot requires top hat.
I might suggest Lock & Co. Hatters, St. James.
- "Lox", as in smoked fish?   - As in "Locked up".
I have trouble understanding you people sometimes.
You all talk so funny.
Gentlemen, would you look after him please?
Now this is a dope-ass top hat.
Gazelle, let's go Ascotting.
Your hat is fine Bill, come on.
Don't make me late for the queen.
Come on, Gazelle. We're gonna be late.
How far is Ascot? How far?
- Merlin said you wanted to see me, sir?   - Sit down.
Pretty dog. What's his name?
- J.B.   - As in "James Bond"?
No.
"Jason Bourne"?
Jack Bauer.
Oh! Bravo.
It pains me to admit it, Eggsy, but I
think that one day you might be as good a spy as any of them.
Take it.
Shoot the dog.
This weapon is live.
Give me the gun.
At least the girl's got balls,
Get out. I knew you couldn't make it.
Go home.
Merlin, send in Roxy, please.
Welcome to Kingsman, Lancelot.
- Mom.   - Eggsy.
Oh god, Where have you been? I've been so worried about you.
Oh my Dais, look how big you've got.
- Where is he?   - I am fine.
Eggsy, please please, just don't get involved...
No, I should never have left you on your own.
This stops right now. Be right back.
Hey Dean
Oh Mugsy, so you're back?
- You nicked a fucking taxi now?   - Yep
Yeah. Can I have a word about my mom's black eye?
You wanna have a word with me, you get out of that cab,
I'll knock you straight back down on your fucking arse.
Tell your muppets to go inside, then I'll get out.
Go on lads. There'll be two hits:
Me and him and then he and the floor.
Come on in, you prick.
Let's see what you got, eh. You wanna beat me?
What are you doing?
Oh no no no come on
Get out of the fucking car. What are you doing?
Now you've gone all bollocks.
Come on, he'll beat my fucking mother.
Come back when you've grown a pair. Mugsy.
You throw away your biggest opportunity over a fucking dog.
And then you humiliate me by stealing my boss's car.
- You shot a dog just to get a fucking job?   - Yes, I did.
Mr Pickle here reminds me of that every time I take a shit.
You shot your dog and now it's stuffed?
You fucking freak.
No. I shot my dog and then I brought him home and continued
to care for him for the next eleven years until he died of pancreatitis.
It was a blank, Eggsy.
It was a fucking blank.
Remember Amelia?
She didn't drown. She works
in our tech department in Berlin. She's fine.
Limits must be tested. A Kingsman
only condones the risking of a life to save another.
As my father saved your life even though your fuck-up cost his?
What you've get him stuffed here also?
Can't you see that everything
I have done has been about trying to repay him?
Harry, listen to this.
Valentine's alarm is saying something of note.
You know what I love about pen and paper?
Nobody can hack into this shit.
Our worldwide tour was a complete success.
We have total coverall.
Like when all your numbers in bingo are crossed out.
Bingo!
Bingo, the game. You have played Bingo, right?
Do I look like I play bingo?
Point is...
if our tests go well at church tomorrow,
we are good to go.
South Glade Mission Church.
- Merlin, get the plane ready.   - Will do
- I am so sorry. I'm gonna do every..   - You should be.
You stay right there. I'll sort this mess out when I get back.
And I say to you: Bear witness.
Watch the news. Watch the news.
AIDS, floods. The blood of the innocents spilled.
And yet there are those who doubt this is the wrath of God.
Our filthy government condones sodomy.
Divorce, abortion.
And yet some still doubt, there is the work of the Antichrist.
You do not have to be a Jew,a nigger, a whore ...
or an atheistic science loving evolution spouter.
Charming ceremony. Do you see Valentine anywhere?
So my friends, although He is a just god,
he is justly no turning back from the...
AMERICA IS DOOMED
Are you sure we are out of range?
We're over a 1000 feet away. What's wrong?
What if the calculations are wrong?
You just have to trust me.
Jews, nigger, fag lovers.
And the devil is burning them for all eternity.
Excuse me.
Where are you going? Hey, what's your problem?
I am a Catholic whore,
currently enjoying congress out of wedlock with my black Jewish boyfriend...
who works in a military abortion clinic.
So hail Satan. And have a lovely afternoon, madam.
Oh shit, he's leaving. I'm starting the test now.
Hope enough of these freaks have our SIM cards.
I ask you to sit down.
Leave this church like the infidel you are.
It seems like the devil will really save you now.
You will eat your babies. You will drown in the blood of the Lord.
He will not save you.
Oh,fuck.
I can't watch this. Get over here.
Jesus. Oh, fuck.
Galahad, can you hear me? Harry!
Harry, what the heck is going on?
Just turn the volume down please.
- I didn't expect it to be that effective.   - What kind of response are we talking of?
100%.
So everyone's been infected whether they have SIM card or not?
And it's added benefit of wiping out the Kingsman.
Not yet.
Oh you need to see this.
What did you do to me? I had no control.
I killed all those people.
- I wanted to.   - Clever, isn't it?
In simple terms, it`s a neurological wave that triggers the centers of aggression
and switches off inhibitus.
Transmitted through your nasty free SIM cards,
I assume?
You know what this look like?
Its like those old movies we both love.
Now I'm gonna tell you my whole plan ...
and then I'm gonna come up with some absurd, convoluted way to kill you...
and then you'll find an equally comnvoluted way to escape.
That sounds good to me.
Well, this ain't that kind of movie.
No.
Is he dead?
That's usually what happens when you shoot someone in the head.
It feels good, huh?
No no, it does not feel good. It felt fucking awful.
What? You just killed how many people in that church.
This is one guy.
No, they killed each other.
Okay, set down the countdown clock. This party starts tomorrow.
Arthur?
- Are you there?   - Sadly, I am.
Assemble the Kingsman.
Can't you see that everything I have done has been about trying to repay him?
I see a young man with potential,
who wants to do something good with his life.
Arthur, Harry is dead.
Galahad is dead.
Hence, we have just drunk a toast to him.
Well then you know what that psycho's doing.
How many people in the world have got those SIM cards?
Valentine can send a signal to any of them; all of them.
If they all go home at the same time, then..
Indeed. And thanks to Galahad's recordings,
we have Valentine's confession.
The intelligence has been passed on to the relevant authorities.
Our work is complete.
And a most distinguished legacy for our fallen friend it is too.
And that's it?
Come sit down, boy.
This is an 1815 Napoleonic brandy.
And we only drink it when we lose a Kingsman.
Galahad was very fond of you.
And on this occasion, I think it is acceptable for us...
to bend the rules a little.
These are all Kingsmen?
Yes, our founder members.
I want you to join me in a toast.
To Galahad.
Harry said you don't like to break the rules, often.
Why now?
You're very good, Eggsy.
Perhaps I'll make you my proposal for Galahad's position.
Provided we can see eye to eye on certain political matters.
Can you guess what this is?
I don't have to. Harry showed it.You click it, I die.
I thought that brandy tasted a bit shit.
Bravo.
Valentine won you over. Somehow
Once he explained, I understood.
When you get a virus, you get a fever.
That's the human body raising its core temperature to kill the virus.
Planet Earth works the same way : Global warming is the fever...
Mankind is the virus. We are making our planet sick.
A cull is our only hope.
If we do not reduce our population ourselves, there's only two ways it can go :
The host kills the virus, or the virus kills the host.
- Either way...   - The result is the same:
The virus dies.
So Valentine's gonna take care of the population problem himself.
If we don't do something, Nature will.
Sometimes a culling is the only way to ensure that this species survives.
And history will see Valentine as the man
who saved humanity from extinction.
And he gets to pick and choose who gets culled, does he?
All his rich mates, they get to live.
And anyone he thinks is worth saving, he's keeping them safe.
- Whether they agree with him or not.   - And you, Eggsy.
In Harry's honor, I am inviting you to be part of a new world.
It's time to make your decision.
I would rather be with Harry. Thanks.
So be it.
The problem with us common types is, that we are light fingered.
Kingsman's taught me a lot. But slight of hand...
Yes, they're our founder members.
...I had that done already.
You dirty little fucking prick.
It's okay, Lancelot. Put it down. It's verified.
Arthur's phone's just received an update text
about getting to safety.
We don't have a lot time.
- What you gonna do?   - The question is what we gonna do.
God knows who's in Valentine's pocket and who's not.
We've no choice.
We are gonna have to deal with this ourselves.
Follow me.
- The fuck is this?   - I have no idea.
What you're playing with...
is a prototype personal trans-atmospheric vehicle.
It was develpoped as part of Reagan's Star Wars project.
It's pretty basic, but it should still work.
We're going to take out one of Valentine's satellites.
We're gonna break the chain, stop the signal.
It will take him a couple of hours to reboot it.
Which buys us enough time for you to
get me into Valentine's mainframe...
so I can shut it down.
Lancelot, you are going to be using it. Get into your halo suit.
The Swedish Prime Minister requesting permisstion to land.
Permission granted.
- Please.   - Thank you.
- So how many more are we expecting?   - Not many. Most have their own bunkers.
I figure we're just getting really nervous once.
Welcome, Prime Minister.
It seems the implant can emit some kind of counter signal...
to ensure the wearer remains unaffected by the waves from the SIM card.
The waves that turns everyone
into a psycho killer?
Quite. But what they probably didn't tell anyone...
is that it can also super heat
their soft tissue at his command.
Valentine's selected his chosen few together countdown a warning.
He had to be sure that it didn't blow up to the wrong people beforehand.
And how does this help us right now?
It doesn't. Roxy, here we go.
The higher you go, The more the balloons expand.
When you reach the edge of the atmosphere, they will explode.
You need to deploy your missile just before that, okay?
The edge of the atmosphere.
And once you've deployed, you'll need to release for descent fast.
Good luck.
You can do this, okay?
Eggsy, come on. Time is not our friend.
Getting in with Arthur's invitation, you'll have to blend in.
- I'm supposed to be Arthur?   - His invitation's in his phone.
Give them this and give his real name:Chester King.
- And what about you?   - I'm the pilot. I'm gonna stay here.
- Is that gonna fit me?   - A bespoke suit always fits.
Just be grateful Harry had it made for you. Get dressed.
The fuck's wrong with them?
I don't know. Could have something to do with mass genocide?
Give me the mic.
Hey yo.
Everybody listen up.
What the fuck wrong with you people?
I just want to remind you that today is a day of celebration.
We must put aside all talks of death, and focus on birth.
The birth of a new age.
We mustn't mourn those who give their lives today.
We should honor their sacrifice.
She got my number to call me back...
And their role in saving the human race.
We must put aside doubts and guilt.
You are the chosen people.
When folks tell their kids the story of Noah's Ark, is Noah the bad guy?
Is God the bad guy?
How about the animals marching two by two?
Of course not.
Yes, that's it. So let's turn that frown upside down.
Eat, drink and party.
And I'll see you all in the new age.
Rox, it`s me. How's the view?
- Hideous.   - Mine's pretty sweet.
- They made you one of these suits yet?   - No, not yet.
You got some to look forward to then.
We're coming up on Valentine's base. Gotta go.
Good luck.
You're looking good, Eggsy.
Feeling good, Merlin.
This is November 2-4-7 Charlie Kilo requesting permission to land.
Permission is granted.
Fuck me.
Eggsy. We're on.
Chester King.
Mr. King, welcome.
I'm sure you've adhered to Mr Valentine's
strict no weapons policy ...
- but if you don't object..   - Of course.
Do you have any luggage?
Congratulations, Mycroft. You just graduated from my pilot to my valet.
- You cheeky.   - Understood? Good.
Thank you.
Eggsy, find a laptop. Get me online. The clock is ticking.
And remember :Try to blend in.
Would sir care for a drink?
Martini. Gin, not vodka, obviously.
Stirred for 10 seconds while glancing it an unopened bottle of vermouth. Thank you.
- Merlin, you clock in this?   - Yes I am. Stay focused.
Lancelot, you're doing great.Not much further to go.
Yes, Merlin.
Eggsy, get me online. Now.
Yep. I'm on it.
Lancelot, you're approaching your altitude limit.
These balloons won't last much longer.
start to engage missile.
The society is dead. Long live society.
Amen to that.
Morten Lindstr.
Chester King. How'd you get online? I couldn't...
Oh well, it's a closed network, you see. For authorized connections only.
I've got a fix on the satellite.
Do you have the correct time? I think I'm still on my last time zone.
Oh yeah. Lets see now.
- Eggsy, I'm in. Get your arse back to the plane now.   - I'm on my way.
Lancelot, good luck. Firing in three, two...
Nice and slow.
What the fuck are you doing here?
Well, my family was naturally invited. Obviously.
Now get the fuck up. Slowly.
Shit. Lancelot, hurry up and fire. The other balloon is gonna blow.
Yes, Merlin. I've nearly got it. Give me a second.
Valentine, I've caught a fucking spy.
V-Glass, zoom.
Oh fuck. It's that young valet.
Son of a bitch.
Got it.
Oh shit. Sound the alarm.
I'm not taking any chances.
Okay, you send out the two-minute warning. I'm starting the override.
Countdown initiated.
- You see him?   - Over here.
Eggsy, take a left. Two guards up ahead.
Lancelot, release now.
Eggsy, straight ahead and then right. There's two more.
Alright, everybody on your feet. Countdown to V-Day.
Welcome into new age.
Downward spiral
Eggsy, next left. Got a narrow tunnel.
Here we go.
Ten...
Nine...
Eight...
Seven...
Six...
Five...
Four...
Three, two, one ...
Nice. Well done, both of you.
It's not working.
It's supposed to be working. What the fuck?
Well done, Rox. Good girl.
We've lost one of our satellites.
Oh no no. There's no way I can hack past that.
What's going on? Is there a problem?
C'mon, there's no need for guns. I'm just a pilot.
Fuck! Merlin!
Get in here.
Come on.
- Let's get the fuck out of here.   - I can't.
I can't get into Valentine's machine. It's got biometric security.
You're gonna have to get in there and make sure his hand never touches that desk.
- You taking a fucking piss?   - I'm afraid not.
Set that then.
This is mine. I'll show you yours.
Good choice.
How long to relink the satellite chain?
It can take an hour. Maybe two.
Bullshit. Just bring these two closer together.
But that's not yours.
V-glass, call E-man.
E, its V. Listen man, I got a little hickup on this end;
I need a piggyback.
One of my satellites just went down but is right next to one of yours.
You read my mind. How long before you make that happen?
Go.
We should be coming back online.
Valentine using someone else's satellite.
He's gonna reconnect the chain. Its gonna take him no time at all.
He sits at 20%.
Eggsy, Valentine's got a present for you. Get a move on.
Is that Kingsman dead yet?
Not yet, but he will be soon.
Good.
Merlin, I'm fucked.
As am I.
They're coming at me from both sides. I'm out of options.
Rox, I need a favor.
Call my mum and tell her
to lock herself away from Dean and the baby.
And tell her I love her.
Oh for fuck sake.
Merlin, you remember those implants you said were of no use to us?
Any chance you could turn them on?
Alright, my turn to play, Valentine.
Oh no. What the fuck is he doing?
I can't stop this.
Yes, please.
SECURITY IMPLANTS ACTIVATED
No!
Oh my god.
That was fucking spectacular.
Merlin, you're a fucking genius.
What the fuck is happening out there?
Aren't you that princess who went missing?
Can you get me out?
Well if I do, will you give me a kiss?
I've always wanted to kiss a princess.
If you get me out right now, I will give you more than just a kiss.
You motherfucker.
Did you really think I was stupid enough to implant one of those things in my own head?
What are you? Fucking crazy?
All those innocent people killed themselves for what?
You didn't stop shit.
Fine, I have locked the door. What do you want me to do now?
As I said, put your daughter in the bathroom and throw away the key.
It's still happening.
- You fucking insane.   - Just do it.
Eggsy, the signal's started.
Get Valentine's hand off that bloody desk now.
Sorry, love. Gotta save the world.
If you save the world, would you do the asshole?
I'll be right back.
Good luck.
London.
Rio.
Get down.
You did it.
This glass is not gonna hold long.
You stay here.
Merlin, quickly. How do I get up there?
Keep shooting. I'll find a route.
Understood.
Holy fuck.
We are back up.
Back up!
This is great.
Eggsy, fucking get off his hand.
Kick his ass, darling.
Seoul, Caracas, Mumbai.
Kill your motherfucker. Kill your all friends.
Eggsy, the world is going to shit.
- Is he dead yet?   - Not yet.
Stop playing with your food. Kill him.
Gazelle. Gazelle
Come on.
Kill him.
Well done son.
Yes. Yes, Eggsy.
Well done, Eggsy. And you, Lancelot.
I am so sorry. Mommy would never hurt you.
Mommy would never hurt you. I am so sorry.
You ok?
Harry would be proud of you, Eggsy.
He was right.
'Sup man?
Is this the part where you say some really bad pun?
It's like you said to Harry:
This ain't that kind of movie, bro.
Perfect.
Eggsy, where're you going? There's no need for champagne. We have got lots on the plane.
- Did you save the world?   - Yes i did.
- You gonna come in?   - Yes, I am.
Merlin, this door's locked. How do I get in?
26 25.
Merlin, you're the governor.
You owe me, Eggsy.
Eggsy?
Oh my world.
Michelle, turn that shit off, its turning me nutsy.
I rather like that song.
Leave it on, Mom.
Mugsy's back.
You finally come to have that word with me, have you son?
Or are you going to run away again and pretend you're getting another coat dress like that?
You mean this?
No.
I know this bloke who's just taken over
a tailor shop up on Seville Road.
He's got me a job, Mom.
Comes with a lot of perks.
Including a house.
Come and live with me there, Mum.
- Come on.   - Sit down, you.
Only place she'll be visting is you in fucking hospital, d'you hear?
Just leave him alone. Eggsy, go please. Just go away.
Alright.
Yes, just do as mommy says.
Find yourself a tailor and think that chicken costume's gonna suit you,
you mug.
As a good friend once said:
Manners...
maketh...
the man.
- Dean?   - Shut the fuck up.
Eggsy, I'm gonna shove your manners up your fucking...
So...
Are we going to stand here all day, or are we going to fight?
1997年 中东
这是零一阿尔法,我们已控制住了猎鹰
重复,我们已经控制住了猎鹰
在我数到十之前
把你知道的所有情报说出来
否则,十就是你最后听到的数字
一、二、三
四、五、六、七、八
手榴弹,快闪开
见鬼
居然没发现
我他妈的我怎么会没发现...
梅林,很抱歉让你身处这般境地
你把他训练得很好
詹姆斯,你的训练结束了
- 欢迎加入皇家特工,兰斯洛特  - 谢谢长官
我会亲自收拾烂摊子的
伦 敦
我表示非常遗憾
你丈夫的英勇事迹无法公之于众
- 希望你能谅解  - 你让我如何去谅解
你什么都不告诉我
我甚至知道他已经不在原来的部队了
恕我不能多言
但我希望你能收下这枚英勇勋章
仔细看背面,那里有一串号码
为了表示感激
我们想要给你...
可以称之为"帮助",帮什么忙由你决定
你只要跟接线员说,"牛津鞋,不要布洛克鞋"
我们就知道是你了
我不想要你的帮助
我只想我的丈夫回来
- 你叫什么名字,小家伙  - 艾格西
你好,艾格西,能给我看看吗
艾格西,你保管好这个,好吗
还有照顾好你妈妈
王 牌 特 工
特 工 学 院
阿根廷 十七年后
非常抱歉,阿尔诺德教授,这确实过分了点
天呐,快拿掉
上头严令禁止伤害你
听着,你们弄错了
我只是一名大学讲师,没什么钱
和钱无关,我们的老板只是想和你聊聊
那我是不是可以放心了
他马上就到,他会解释的
你喜欢威士忌吗,里德,来一杯六二年的达尔摩
真的,这酒非常好喝
你会喜欢的
我想找你们借一杯糖的话,不算是太过分吧
阿尔诺德教授,我是来接你回家的
1962年的达尔摩,洒出一点都是罪过
你觉得呢
能帮我拿着这些吗
谢谢
全都收拾好了
我喜欢的欢迎方式
血腥暴力让我倒胃口,绝非夸张
要是我看到一滴血,那我就完了
我会条件反射般的...狂吐
听着,十分抱歉让你目睹这令人不快的场面
都怪这个不速之客,但我承诺
等我查出他为谁效力时
你和我会成为好朋友的
请载我到店里
萨维尔街 一号
威斯敏斯特市[伦敦内自治市]
注: 萨维尔街是世界最顶级西服手工缝制圣地
金士曼裁缝店
亚瑟在餐厅里,先生
- 亚瑟  - 加拉哈德
其它人都开始在想
你不来的话,我们是否要再次举杯致敬了
先生们,我很欣慰,过去的十七年里我们
没有机会用这个酒瓶
兰斯洛特是一位杰出的特工,一个名副其实的王牌特工
我们会深切怀念他,敬兰斯洛特
敬兰斯洛特
我打算明天开始选拨
替代兰斯洛特位置的人
我希望你们每个人
都提名一位候选人,并上报给英国总部
最晚不超过格林威治时间晚上九点前,谢谢
梅林,请进
兰斯洛特当时在调查一伙雇佣军
他们一直在进行生化武器的实验
先生们,请戴上眼镜
2012年,乌干达,合成卡西酮[毒品]
被用于污染了陆军基地的供给水源
狂怒,同类相食,导致多人死亡
2013年,车臣,叛乱分子相互攻击
毫无疑问,也是这些雇佣兵的杰作
但没有查出任何化学制品
那兰斯洛特是怎么死的
在追踪过程中,他发现了他们在阿根廷的房产
在监视他们的同时
还察觉到他们实施了一起绑架案
于是他单独执行了营救任务,结果失败了
这是他最后传送回来的画面
绑架受害者是詹姆斯·阿尔诺德教授
- 他是谁  - 某个气候变化预言家
提出了某种叫盖亚理论的假说
盖亚假说由英国大气学家
詹姆斯·洛夫洛克在20世纪60年代末提出
认为世界能够自愈之类的
但让人好奇的是,他并未真正失踪
这就是阿尔诺德教授
今天早上出现在帝国理工学院
这交给你了,还有不要忘了上交候选人提名
这次尽量挑个更合适的人选
十七年都过去了
你仍然不打算与时代同步
我提醒你
如果不是那个年轻人,我今天也不会坐在这里
他是一块当王牌特工的料,甚至要比其他人更优秀
但他最终没能成为我们的一员,不是吗
面对现实吧,加拉哈德,你的小实验失败了
恕我直言,亚瑟,可你真是个势利小人
- 恕你直言  - 世界正在改变
贵族们都长着短小下巴是有原因的
短下巴被视作性格软弱
艾格西
艾格西,出来一下
- 还有卷纸吗  - 没有
为什么不帮你妈
去楼下商店买点呢
- 你自己去买  - 嘿
和你说过不要这样和迪恩说话
三个人多挤,怎么不叫迪恩的走狗去买
要不这样吧
拿着这些钱
去买卷纸,顺便给你自己买点糖
你出去之后
我会让你妈妈见识下我们三人也能相处甚欢
谢谢宝贝
来吧
给你这个
好点了吧
迪恩对你妈这么差,她为什么不离开他
缺乏自尊,这就是问题所在
滚蛋,她怎么可能没自尊呢
他妈可性感了
- 不要见怪,伙计  - 没关系
总有一天,我要打烂他的脸
兄弟,你疯了吗
他会找那些家伙来对付你
然后假装自己什么都...不知情
别以为我们老大在泡艾格西的老妈
你们在这瞎掰掰,我们不敢对你怎么样
- 差不多吧  - 别这样
我们走吧,伙计,不值得
你们在这里坐得够久了,滚吧
怎么
抱歉,不好意思咯
垃圾
不值得跟他们一般见识,兄弟
外面冷死了,我们为什么要走路呢
你这家伙偷了他的车钥匙
没错,我们还要玩坏他的车
见鬼
等等,伙计们
妈的那车是我的
艾格西
我发誓,你们麻烦大了
你他妈的死定了
停下来
我他妈要杀了你
狂飙吧,艾格西
迪恩,是我
他妈艾格西刚偷了我的车
我在酒吧门口,他当着我的面
原地转了十五圈,然后直接把车开走了
他不尊敬我,就是在蔑视你
慢着,什么...
见鬼
狐狸不是什么好东西,你应该直接碾压过去的
我应该做的事情可多了
剩下的交给我,你们下车
快他妈下车
艾格西,小偷可没有正义同盟可言
你最好供出
当时和你一起的同伙名单...
要么你蹲监狱,这完全取决于你
我想行使我打电话的权利
我希望是打给你妈的
告诉她,你要十八个月后才能回家吃晚饭了
客户投诉部,请问有什么能帮你
我叫艾格西·安文,对不起,是加里·安文
我遇到大麻烦了,我现在在市区的警察局
我妈说如果我需要帮助可以打这个电话...
对不起,先生,你打错电话了
等等
"牛津鞋,不要布洛克"
您的投诉已受理
希望我们不会失去您这样的忠实客户
警察局
什么
但是...好
是的,我完全理解
艾格西.
- 要搭便车回家吗  - 你是谁
- 保释你出来的人  - 你还没有回答我的问题
如果你能礼貌地说声谢谢就好了
我的名字是哈利·哈特,那勋章是我给你的
你的父亲救过我的命
上好的麦芽酒和黑啤
那你做裁缝之前,参过军吗,像军官那种
不完全是
你们当时被派遣去了哪,伊拉克还是别的地方
抱歉,艾格西,这是机密
但是我爸救了你一命,是吧
你父亲去世那天,是我疏忽了
如果不是他挺身而出
我的错误会让在场的所有人都付出生命的代价
所以是我欠他的
你父亲是个勇敢的人,还是个好人
查阅了你的档案后,我觉得
你父亲他肯定会对你选择的人生失望透顶
你没资格这样说我
高智商,小学时表现极为出色
然后一切都颠倒了
吸毒,小偷小摸,游手好闲
你以为工作满大街都是吗
这解释不了你为何放弃了你的爱好
你连续两年蝉联地区举办的十岁以下儿童
体操比赛第一名
你教练曾视你为奥运队的人才
是啊,成长时期有那样一个继父在身边
很快就会学到新的爱好
总是把错误推到别人身上
你退队又该埋怨谁呢
你的训练才进行了一半,而且成绩优秀,但你却放弃了
因为我妈变得神经兮兮的
怕我会像我爸一样离她而去
我们才不会给你们这样的势利小人当炮灰
你们总是高高在上的,对我这样的人指手画脚
但从没想过我们这样做的原因
我们别无选择,知道吗
如果我们和你一样,含着银汤匙出身
即使不比你优秀,至少也能和你一样
你他妈的还敢来这儿,好大的胆子
这些年轻人也是
只要有银制灵药就能成功的例子吗
不,他们是例外,走吧
为何,我们还没喝完呢
你偷了他的车那一刻起
迪恩说他不会罩你了,我才不管你妈怎样给你求情
听着,小伙子们
我今天心情不太好,所以
不管你们对艾格西有什么不满,我相信都是事出有因的
如果你们能让我们单独待会....
让我好好喝完这杯可口的吉尼斯黑啤
我将不胜感激
你最好少管闲事,老头子
拳头可是不长眼
他不是开玩笑的,你走吧
借过
如果你想找个牛郎玩玩
可以去史密斯街的转角处看看
不知礼
无以
立也
知道这句话的意思吗
不知道的话让我就给你上一课吧
我们是要这样傻站一整天
还是要来痛快打一架
你妈逼去死,他妈个王八蛋
击昏
消除记忆
不好意思,我只是需要发泄一下
昨天我有个朋友去世了
其实他也认识你父亲
真的很抱歉,艾格西
我不该当着你面大打出手的
不,拜托,我什么也不会说
我发誓,从这一刻起,我会保持沉默
你不会告诉别人吗
事实上,我从没出卖过别人
- 这是承诺吗  - 我以性命担保
不胜感激,艾格西
你说我是势利小人的话是正确的,但是也有例外
祝你一切好运
名人新闻,里奇蒙德·瓦伦丁的电影
昨晚在好莱坞首映
这个关于网络大亨崛起的故事
是本季度获奖热门
值得注意的是伊奇·阿萨里亚没有出席红毯仪式
她在三天前就行踪不明...
也没有出现在她个人的奥克兰演唱会上
至今仍未收到有关赎金的要求...
艾格西,快走,快,他要...
- 求你了,别伤害他  - 滚开  - 别打他了
滚开,给我他妈的闭嘴
他妈的酒吧里和你一起的家伙是谁
我要知道和你在一起的老东西是谁
就我一个人
- 是谁  - 我他妈的不知道你在说什么
我不知道你在说什么
妈的,快说出他的名字
我他妈的不知道你在说什么
听好了,我要你告诉我在酒吧里
和你在一起的是谁,听懂了没
妈的告诉我他的名字
我发誓我要宰了你
- 说啊  - 我他妈不知道你在说什么
- 告诉我  - 快告诉他吧,艾格西
滚开,滚开
我现在就可以杀了你,而且没人会知道
但我知道
我手上掌握的证据足够让你在监狱里度过余生
- 迪恩·安东尼·贝克先生  - 妈的是谁说话
所以我建议你离那男孩远点
不然我只能把证据送到相关部门那里
艾格西,去我跟你说过的裁缝店来见我
这他妈的到底什么情况
妈的我看你这次怎么逃
艾格西来了
过来
你个该死的,被我抓到你就死定了
金士曼裁缝店
我从来没见过裁缝
但我知道你肯定不是
跟我来
进来啊
你看见什么了
一个想知道这他妈是怎么回事的人
我看见了一个有潜力的年轻人
一个忠诚的年轻人
他可以完成使命而且想有所作为
你看过电影"颠倒乾坤"吗
没有
那"尼基塔"呢,"风月俏佳人"呢
好吧
我想说的是
没有含着银汤勺出生让你的人生有点曲折艰难
但你可以选择改变
只要你准备好适应并学习,你就可以逆转
就像"窈窕淑女"里面那样吗
你真让人惊喜,对,就像"窈窕淑女"那样
现在,我给你一个成为王牌特工的机会
- 裁缝吗  - 王牌特工
- 像间谍一样  - 类似
- 感兴趣吗  - 你觉得我还有可担心的吗
从1849年起,金士曼就为
世界上最有权势的人服务
在1919年,他们中的一大部分人
在一战中失去了继承人
这意味着一大笔钱没有人继承
许多掌权者都想要保卫和平,保护生命
而我们的创建者意识到
他们可以利用财富和影响力帮助更多的人
我们的冒险就这样开始了
一个拥有最高度自由裁判权的独立国际情报机构
没有政治和官僚主义
专门瓦解政府手下的间谍组织
西装是现代绅士的铠甲
王牌特工就是新时代的骑士
- 这他妈究竟有多深  - 非常深
糟糕,我们迟到了
你爸爸也有过这种表情
我也有过
来吧
加拉哈德,我的代号
- 又迟到了,先生  - 祝你好运
进去吧
集合
女士们先生们,我是梅林
你们即将经历的可能是这世上最危险的工作面试
你们当中仅有一人会成为下一个兰斯洛特
有人知道这是什么吗,你说
- 运尸袋,先生  - 正确
- 查理是吧  - 是的,先生
很好,一会儿你们每人拿一个运尸袋
写上自己的名字
你们还要在那个袋子上写上自己亲人的资料
这意味着你们了解自己将面临的风险
也表示你们同意遵守严格的保密协定
如果不小心打破了协定
你和你的亲人就用得上那个袋子了
明白了吗
很好,解散
洛克希恩尼,但叫我洛克希吧
- 我叫艾格西  - 蛋蛋  - 不,是艾格西
蛋蛋,他们是在哪儿找到你的
你知道我们不能谈论推荐我们的人
那我们得把他灭口
查理只是在闲聊,是吧,查理
- 我叫迪格比  - 迪格比
蛋蛋,这是卢夫斯,卢夫斯,这是蛋蛋
- 那么蛋蛋,你来自牛津还是剑桥  - 都不是
圣安德鲁斯,达勒姆
等等我觉得我们可能见过
在温切斯特加油站的麦当劳那儿是你给我点餐的吗
不是
一定是在圣安德鲁斯
- 别理他们  - 你要笔吗
- 谢谢  - 艾美利亚,是吗
艾美利亚,这是艾格西
你好,艾格西
- 别理那些家伙  - 这也是我要告诉他的
这只是唬人的把戏
军队惯用的手段,没人会死
真遗憾
太好了,所以你不知道,中情局不知道
没人知道这人是谁了吗
没事,真的,没事
并不是完全没事,但我不是为这来的
哥们你了解我,我的问题不是钱
我本可以直接从麻省理工退休
找一个小岛颐养天年,让生意自己运作去吧
没有人让我去拯救地球,是我自己想做的
研究气候变化,游说政客,不断砸钱
你知道为什么我放弃了吗
因为我上一次检查的时候,地球还是一团糟
所以我顿悟了
钱是解决不了问题的
那些自称为政治家的白痴们,他们都是缩头乌龟
除了改选什么也不支持
所以过去两年中我试着寻找一个真正的解决方案
而我找到了
现在,如果你真的想让世界变得更美好
我建议你们竖起耳朵听好了
因为我马上就要告诉你们了
继续,瓦伦丁先生,我还在听
只要你同意我所有的要求
别惊慌,听我说,冷静
妈的
- 通气管  - 通气管
- 淋浴器喷头  - 淋浴器喷头
她是对的,走,快走
去拉一下那道破门如何
恭喜完成第一个任务
查理,洛克希,干得好
那些还没搞清楚情况的人听好了
要是你用通气管插到马桶的U型部分
你就有了无限的空气供给
简单的物理知识,好好记住
艾格西,发现那是个双向镜子真是好样的
我见得多了去了
你们可以把脸上的傻笑收回去
因为在我看来你们每一个人都失败了
你们都忘了最重要的事情
团队合作
好像不是经典军队唬人手段
35、105
就这样,就是这样
你好,有什么可以帮到你
是的,我有个关于人类起源对地球影响的问题
真的吗,这个问题很值得探讨
我的同事为了营救你而牺牲了
你一定见识过他是多么的训练有素
所以我建议你告诉我是谁绑架了你
他们又为什么放了你
我不知道你在说什么
我不能说,那是...
看在上帝的份上,我根本没用力,这人怎么...
植入物已激活
去他妈的,不管他是谁,我会...
居然逼我杀了阿尔诺德教授
我最他妈爱的阿尔诺德教授
好消息是我们知道应急和监控系统运行良好
你知道什么不是好消息吗
"我的同事牺牲了",他那么说的
这是个组织,他们正在全力追踪我们
你跟哪些机构联系了...
我说了,我联系克格勃(苏联),军情六处(英国)
摩萨德(以色列)和北京
- 他们都坚称那不是他们的人  - 北京
中国秘密情报机关连个标识性的名字都没有
还真是吓人啊
不过,这样才叫秘密组织,对吧
你知道吗
让他们去死吧,我们得加快进度,把产品发布提前
他们还在生产过程中,如果加快进度要花一大笔钱的
你看我像在乎钱的样子吗,照我说的做
正如你们昨晚所学到的一课
在特工学院,团队合作至高无上
在这里我们会增强你们的技巧,测试你们的极限
所以你们要选一只小狗
无论你去哪儿,你的狗都跟着你
你要照顾它,训练它
等它们训练有素之时,你们的训练也完成了
那是特指你们当中能或者完成训练的人
都明白了吗,去挑选一只小狗吧
- 狮子狗吗  - 怎么,它们可是猎犬
最古老的工作犬种,容易训练
哈巴狗吗
好歹也是条斗牛犬,不是吗
它还是会长大的吧,不是吗
见鬼
核磁共振没有显示脑震荡的症状
甚至没有直接脑外伤
他多久能出院
回答这个问题得花上百万去研究一下
我们不知道他在那儿遭受了什么攻击
哈利的录像呢
没发回到他家的终端吗
加密了,没法破解
要是他醒过来了
或许你能找他问出密码
他会没事的对吗
我们得有耐心,艾格西,但希望还在
要是我是你,我就专心训练,通过测试,让他骄傲
来吧,J.B.,来吧
我不要因为你变最后一名
J.B.,再不走信不信我他妈毙了你
梅林说我们不准抱着你们跑
放他的狗屁
水又来了
找茬是吧
艾格西,算了吧
怎么了哥们,开不起玩笑啦
真的,你会被开除,这根本不值得
也许我他妈根本不在乎被开除
真的吗,来吧,人生玩家
查理,滚开
滚远点,白痴
好啦,J.B.,没事啦
你们有一小时整来完成测试,现在开始
新目标,800米
真是难以置信,你还在这里
跟一坨屎一样,冲都冲不走
收到,目标已确认,你他妈就不能闭嘴吗
正面差别待遇,真不值得
就像有些人能进高等学府
仅因为他们的老妈是一个断了腿的同性恋
你他妈又不了解我的阶级
哦,抱歉,我很肯定你接受过高等教育
准备好就开枪
这样的正面差别待遇如何
谢谢二位的倾听
我非常非常感谢您远道而来,尊敬的公主殿下
您也一样,首相先生
我觉得这个构想很绝妙
这绝对是个绝妙的构想
你完全疯掉了吧
首相先生,请你清醒一点
你竟然会考虑这样的事情,真是让我惊讶
- 不,别碰我...  - 抱歉,公主殿下...
要将斯堪的纳维亚地区拉回正轨
你的角色至关重要
你备受人民爱戴,具有感召力以及激励民众的能力
如今不管你参不参加...
我需要把你长期安置在一个能保证你的安全的地方
你呢,首相先生,你是否要加入呢
我觉得此时此刻,作为一名政治家,是该作出行动
- 真正去改变世界了  - 太对了
把她带走
- 喝一杯吗  - 好啊
警卫们,救救我
别担心,公主不会受到任何伤害的
反正我支持共和政体,所以真的无所谓
放开公主
好了,搞定了,不疼对吗
- 我都没什么感觉  - 欢迎加入
荣幸之至
进来之前不知道敲门吗
我计划入室抢劫前才会敲门踩点
梅林说你要见我
我希望J.B.的训练和你一样顺利
坐下
恭喜你成为最后六个候选人之一
你的成绩比我预期的还要好
进来
艾格西,我要和哈利单独谈几句,你回避一下
不用了,让他待着,说不定能学到点什么
悉随尊便,来看看这个
看在上帝的份上,我几乎没碰你,这人怎么...
我靠,这也太过分了,哈利
你把他头都爆了,这有点过了,不是吗
实际上,爆炸是他脖子上的植入物引起的
在这儿,就在伤疤下面
我的装备捕捉到它的触发信号了吗
很幸运地捕捉到了
但很不幸的是
所追踪到的注册IP地址登记在瓦伦丁公司名下
这线索没什么用,他们在全世界有几百万的员工
不,里奇蒙德·瓦伦丁是个天才
你们都没看他今天的发布会吗
没有
我们一年花在手机和网络上的费用平均要两千美元
在此我很荣幸向大家宣布
这样的时代要结束了
从明天开始,每个男人,女人,还有孩子都能
拿到一张免费的
适用于所有手机和电脑的电话卡
而且可以免费使用我公司的通讯服务
免费电话,免费网络,人人共享
永久有效
瓦伦丁的助理也有相同的植入物疤痕
我觉得我要和瓦伦丁先生来一次单独会晤了
他下周有一场晚宴
我帮你搞一张邀请函,但是你要万分小心
在你卧床期间,已有上百个重要人物失踪了
没有勒索信,和阿尔诺德教授的情况如出一辙
那我建议你给我编造一个值得绑架的身份
- 你恐高吗  - 是的,还可以,但我以前做过
要是我不想着可能还好一点
嘿,你会没事的,你是成绩最优异的学员之一
听好,你们的任务是避开雷达的追踪
降落在指定地点
如果我在雷达上追踪到你们
或者没降落到指定地点,那就打包回家吧
都明白了吗
即将到达降落区域,还有二十秒
出发了
艾格西,我觉得我真的不行
你当然不行
闪到后面去,我来教教你怎么做
- 来吧  - 跳吧
艾格西,等等,等一下
洛克希,别想太多了
跟着我跳,好吗
来吧
洛克希,现在不跳就没机会了
跳啊
好姑娘,洛克希,真高兴你做到了
好极了
哦,你们看起来心情都不错嘛,真以为会这么简单吗
白痴都能看懂屏幕上的数字
身为王牌特工,你得学会在高压环境下解决问题
比方说你们之中有一个人
没有降落伞的情况下该怎么办
什么,没有降落伞,是谁
- 操,是谁  - 我们该怎么办
我告诉过你们要降落在目标上
而且不能被雷达发现
希望我不用将
某人从地上铲出来
但如果你真能摔进目标里
我会对你刮目相看的
所有人听着,我有个法子
两人一组,抓住离你最近的人
卢夫斯,快点
我操
卢夫斯
真该死,我过不来
我操
谢天谢地
卢夫斯,你这个卑鄙小人
我们现在成了奇数了,围成一圈吧
操,好吧兄弟们,就这么做
我们轮流打开降落伞
找到那个倒霉蛋后,右手边的人就抓住他
好的,艾格西
好主意,艾格西,你们还有三十秒
马上开始吧,快点
我先
操
警告 高度过低
下一个是我
地面上见,兄弟们
该我了
操
洛克希,不管发生什么,我都会抓住你,好吗
好的,艾格西
- 你先来,好吗  - 好
艾格西,洛克希
我操
操
坚持住
雨果,迪格比,你们没落在K字标记上
那就不能成为K的一员
卢夫斯,你开伞太早,完全暴露在雷达上了
你们三个,收拾东西回家吧
艾格西,洛克希,恭喜你们,你们创造了新纪录
直到300尺才开伞,够胆量
漂亮地完成了又一项任务,解散吧
抱歉长官,但你们他妈为什么选我当倒霉蛋
我这个候选人的命就这么不值钱
不不不,别这么跟我说话
如果你要抱怨,到我耳边小声来说
我来给你减轻一些负担吧
德福里先生,见到你真高兴
抱歉,我想我把日子记错了
哦,不不,因为你的光临,我特地把晚宴取消了
捐赠了这么多钱的人值得我为他准备一场私人晚宴
请进
谢谢
我得说,我十分期待和你见面
没有几个亿万富翁是我不认识的
我想也是
很显然,我让我的人去查了查你的生意
发现您出身自一个富贵世家
你是怎么赚到的
主要是不动产,房地产市场
没什么好隐瞒,如果你想知道的话
啊,听着,我只是好奇你是个什么样的人
我想你能理解的
- 我理解  - 希望你饿了
- 我饿坏了  - 好极了,请坐吧
- 请给我来一份巨无霸  - 选得好
但是没什么能敌得过两份秘制酱料的吉士汉堡
- 和四五年的拉菲简直是绝配  - 经典搭配
我推荐夹心面包
搭配1937年滴金酒庄的酒作为甜点
我喜欢
你想捐钱给我的基金会是吗
你应该知道我把这片地区的事项都停止了吧
气候变化会影响着我们所有人,瓦伦丁先生
而你是为数不多的和我想法一致的有权势之人
我中断项目是因为没什么进展
每一个研究最后都指向相同的结论
碳排放只是个幌子
无论我们做什么补救方法都只是徒劳
你还挺懂的
有时候我还挺嫉妒那些对自己的领域一无所知的人
就像阿尔诺德常说的
"人类是唯一知道宿主的死期
却还要带着这样的恐怖诅咒苟活的病毒"
可没多少人知道他
你喜欢间谍电影吗,德福里先生
现在的间谍电影对我来说都有点太严肃了
但那些老电影...精彩无比
随时都能为我展示难以想象的戏剧化情节
那些老邦德电影,哦,天哪
我还是个孩子时,那可是我的梦想职业
一个绅士间谍
但我总觉得是反派角色造就了老邦德电影的辉煌
在我还是个孩子的时候
我总是幻想自己是个未来主义的自大狂
可我们都要长大,真是遗憾
祝你好胃口
再给我几天去考虑一下你的提议
我会让人和你的人进行联系,然后就算谈妥了
感谢这一顿,愉快的用餐[麦当劳快乐儿童餐]
- 你想让我跟踪他吗  - 不用
我在酒里放了纳米追踪器
接下来的二十四小时我们都会知道他的一举一动
最终会查出来他为谁工作了
瓦伦丁根本不让我离开他的视线
我在进去时只拍到这个
南林地使命教会是个仇恨团体,总部在肯塔基州
联邦调查局已经监视他们好几年了
你觉得瓦伦丁是他们的资助人吗
不知道,我还没发现他们有关联的直接证据
但我会继续追查的
哦,顺便一提,失踪名单又增加了一人
现在多了斯堪的纳维亚的皇室成员
迪尔德公主殿下
放我出去,你这个疯子
我说过了,你想什么时候出来都可以
- 只要你同意我的条件  - 我不同意
而且我也永远不会同意
好吧
贱货
我们要见英国大使
最近几周,失踪的名流人数还在继续增加
与日俱增的压力迫使各国领导人作出回应
我们在竭尽所能寻找迪尔德公主
世界各国的政府和安全部队正在共同协作
寻找这些绑架案的幕后黑手
另一方面,全世界的人们都在
不分昼夜地排队领取免费的电话卡
P女士,你拿到卡了
是啊,我排了一整天的队了
慈善家里奇蒙德·瓦伦丁发起的史无前例的慷慨馈赠
目前已经对外发送了十亿张电话卡
稍息
你们以为今天的任务都完成了吗
大概还没
- 派对  - 就在今晚,在伦敦
- 这是谁  - 你们的目标
你们的任务是利用你们学过的
神经语言程序学知识去俘获照片中的人
我说的"俘获",指的是肉体关系上的
小意思
- 女孩都喜欢糙汉子  - 那我们走着瞧
那是一定的
你好,抱歉,我必须要过来说一句
"你的眼睛真是太美了"
- 你带美瞳了吗  - 没有
- 你肯定戴了  - 天哪,负面打压,这可搞笑了
九十年代之后我就没见过有人尝试这么搭讪了
你说什么
"负面打压",即用一些负面的语言
来打压漂亮女孩的社会价值
这会让你想要赢得他的认可
可笑的基础语言神经学伎俩
只有我觉得这个香槟味道很奇怪吗
每人爱好不同,哥们
我想是因为这酒太廉价了
你可以尝尝这个,味道很不错
如果你对色诱技巧感兴趣的话
这家伙就是教科书范本
知道他刚才做了什么吗,这叫做"意见式开场"
他用一个中性的问题来和你搭讪
然后让大家都加入谈话
因此你会注意到他这个人
不是这样的,我只是在说香槟味道很怪
索菲小姐,我是蒙塔戈·贺林
接待处有电话找你
- 马上回来  - 待会儿见
待会见
干得不错,洛克希,我现在感觉不太好
你还好吧
抱歉偷听你们说话
但是想要把人带回家还有一个更简单有效的方法
用迷幻药
或者药效更加强劲的东西
你他妈的是谁
我在哪
这把刀可以救你的命
操
我雇主想问你两个问题,艾格西
金士曼是什么,哈利·哈特又是谁
我不知道那是什么鬼
艾格西,我刚杀了你那两个朋友
因为他们也给我这样一个胡扯的答案
快把绳子割断,求你了
嘿,艾格西,金士曼值得你为之献身吗
去你妈的
恭喜,做得非常好
- 其他人怎么样  - 洛克希完美地通过了测试
查理是下一个,想看好戏吗
好啊
王牌特工真值得你送死吗
不,他妈的不值得,我操,你问什么我都说,求你放开我
切斯特·金就是亚瑟
间谍机构的首领
间谍机构叫做金士曼,快点放开我
谢谢你,查理,非常感谢
放开我啊,不是他妈说好的吗
不
我对你寄予了厚望,你这个不争气的废物
很抱歉,求你给我解开绳子
自己解吧
亚瑟,亚瑟,求你了
知道我爸是谁吗,老混蛋
有人吗,来人啊
加拉哈德,帕西瓦尔,恭喜
你们的候选人已经
到了测试最后一个阶段
按照传统,你们现在可以和他们共处二十四个小时
艾格西,你要知道你父亲也曾走到这个阶段
现在开始,没有任何安全保障,懂了吗
很好,解散
查理,是时候回家了
去你妈的
我老爸会知道的
"尿还是不尿"
这是我在巴黎
丢下一个脏弹后的头条新闻
德国队对英格兰队,1:5
我错过了那场比赛
我当时在五角大楼执行一项调查间谍的任务
我的首次任务,我阻止了
针对玛格丽特·撒切尔的暗杀行动
并非所有人都因此而感激你
艾格西,重点是根本不会有人会因为这些任务而感激我
所有报纸的头版都只会是名人的无聊八卦
因为这是金士曼的本质
我们得深藏功与名
一个绅士的名字
只能在报纸上出现三次
出生时,结婚时和死亡时
首要的是,我们是绅士
那真是的没戏了
就像查理说的,我只是一介平民
不是的,成为一名绅士
和一个人的出身没有丝毫关系
成为一名绅士只需要学习
对,但怎么学呢
好吧,第一课
你在就坐前应该要先问问我
第二课,学做美味可口的马提尼[鸡尾酒]
好的,哈利
我了个擦,痛死老子了
是你自己要求用生物识别的
安全系统,弄个简单的开关都不行吗
简单的开关,这可是一台极其危险的机器
只有像我一样富有责任心且理智的人才能操作
要是落到坏人手中,就会发生不幸的灾难
掌纹同步完成
可以走了吗,妈的
还没,现在看下这个,测试下教会那边
这台是短程操作机器,用简单开关就行
你要像窈窕淑女那样教我咬字发音说话得体吗
没那么荒唐
成为绅士和口音没关系
就算赤身裸体也能从容不迫,这才是绅士
就像海明威说的那样
比自己同伴优秀,没什么可高尚的
真正的高尚是比曾经的自己更优秀
现在,成为绅士需要的第一样东西就是合身得体的西装
我说的是定制西装,而不是直接买的现货
金士曼的西装通常都防弹
先去量下尺寸
无论你能不能得到这份职业
在金士曼训练的日子会给你留下难忘而且有用的回忆
很抱歉,先生,但是试衣间有人
- 二号试衣间能用  - 这是他的第一次试衣
怎能用二号试衣间呢
等待期间不如我带你去参观下三号试衣间吧
- 这次是要下还是上  - 都不是
就这样吗
当然不是,扳下你左手边的挂钩
哇哦,非常非常赞
你需要双鞋子来搭配西装
有鞋带的都可称作牛津鞋
这种有额外装饰的叫做布洛克皮鞋
- "只穿牛津鞋,不穿布洛克  - 一生铭记"
艾格西,这话要一生铭记着
试试这双
顺便说下,你武器测试分数非常好
这些你已经很熟悉了
这是我们常规任务的配备手枪
很独特,正如你所见
这种枪也能用猎枪弹在复杂的近距范围进行射击
- 合脚吗  - 恩,不错
那你来展示一下德国贵族的正式问候礼吧
不是这样的,艾格西
真酷炫
以前,特工们的鞋后跟还有电话呢
我要怎么收回去
这东西上面涂有
对人类最致命的神经毒素之一,千万要小心
我觉得这东西相当有趣好玩
是我们化学工程中最精致的典范之一
毒药,服下的时候不会发作
但在最适合的时机之下
你就可以远程启动
预备模式
致命模式
那这些呢,是干嘛用的,电击别人吗
- 别开玩笑了,这是手榴弹  - 真的假的
如果你想电击别人的话,那得用纹章戒指
按照绅士的传统,纹章戒指应该要戴在左手上
但金士曼戴哪只手都行,只要戴得顺手
你只要触碰戒指后面的感应器
戒指就会放出50000伏电
那些呢,有什么特别之处
没有,那只是特工界的时尚工艺品
放回去,艾格西
时间刚好,这位绅士正试完衣服
德福里先生
真巧啊,我就是因为你才来这的
你离开我家后
我一直在找你那天穿着的那件酷毙的外套
刚好我要去参加英国皇家赛马会
很显然我需要一件这样的无尾礼服...
于是我就来这了,你在这里干嘛呢
你好啊,我是里奇蒙德·瓦伦丁
这是我新的贴身男仆,我刚把他介绍给我裁缝
又是一个巧合,我也带了个贴身仆人
你有没有
- 进一步考虑我的提议  - 当然有啊
我手下马上
就会和你联系了,我向你保证
提醒一句,参加赛马会需要戴大礼帽
我向你推荐圣詹姆斯街上的洛克帽子店
- 你是说烟熏鱼吗  - 是与落网的"落"同音的字
有时候我听不懂你们这种人说的话
腔调都古古怪怪的
先生,有劳你帮他试衣
现在我有一顶炫酷的大礼帽了
葛希尔,我们出发去赛马会吧
你的帽子很好看,快点
我要去见女王,别害我迟到了
快啊,葛希尔,我们要迟到了
去赛马会有多远,有多远
- 先生,梅林说你想见我  - 坐下
这狗真可爱,叫什么名字
- J.B.  - 是詹姆斯·邦德(007)的缩写吗
不是
那是杰森·伯恩(谍影重重)吗
是杰克·鲍尔(24小时)
哦,不错
虽然我不太想承认,艾格西
但我觉得你可以成为像他们那样出色的特工
拿着
开枪把狗打死
枪已上膛
把枪给我
至少那女孩都比你有种
出去,我就知道你下不了手
回家吧
梅林,请洛克希进来吧
欢迎加入皇家特工,兰斯洛特
- 妈  - 艾格西
天啊,你都去了哪里了,我担心死你了
哦小黛西,你都长这么大了
- 他在哪  - 我没事
艾格西,求你了,别管我们的事了...
不,我就不该留你独自一人在这里的
现在该结束这一切了,我很快回来
喂,迪恩
小兔崽子,你回来了啊
- 你现在连出租车都偷了吗  - 是啊
是的,我要和你谈谈我妈眼睛上的淤青是怎么回事
你想跟我谈的话,先下车
老子要把你揍得屁滚尿流
让你的走狗先回避,我就下车
走吧,伙计们,你们只会听到两声响
一个是我揍他的声音,另一个是他倒地的声音
放马过来,小混蛋
我看你有没有长进,你想打我吗
你在干嘛
哦,不,不,不,不要
快从车里滚出来啊,你在搞什么鬼
你这个没种的孬货
快停下来,他还会继续打我妈的
有种了再回来找我吧,小瘪三
就因为他妈的一条狗,你放弃了一个大好机会
然后你又偷我老板的车,让我蒙羞
- 你为了得到工作竟然枪毙了一条狗  - 是的
每次我干了坏事,皮克尔都会提醒我那段经历
你杀了自己的狗还把它做成标本了
你这个变态
不是,我对它开了一枪后,把它带回家好生照顾
直到十一年前,它患胰腺炎去世
枪里没有装子弹,艾格西
他妈的没有装子弹
还记得艾美利亚吗
她并没有溺亡
她在柏林的技术部任职,她活得好好的
必须得测试你们的极限
金士曼只会在拯救同伴生命是才会拿自己的性命去冒险
就像我父亲即使要赔上自己的命还是要救你那样吗
你也把他做成标本存放在这里了吗
难道你看不出来
我至今所做的一切都是为了补偿他吗
哈利,听好了
在瓦伦丁身上的窃听器中获得了一些重要信息
知道我为什么喜欢用纸笔吗
因为没人知道我写了什么
我们的环球游说之旅大获成功
各国政要名人都被我们拿下了
就像当你在玩宾果游戏时所有号码都被划掉
宾果:一种填格子游戏
第一个成功者以喊宾果表示取胜
宾果
宾果游戏啊,你玩过那游戏,对吧
我看起来像玩宾果游戏的人吗
重点是
如果我们明天在教堂的测试顺利的话
就可以放手大干了
南林地使命教堂
- 梅林,准备好飞机  - 好的
- 很抱歉,我会...  - 你是该感到抱歉
你待在这里,等我回来时再处理你的破事
美国 肯塔基州
我来告诉你们,这就是证据
看看新闻,都看看新闻
艾滋,洪灾,还有无辜生命挥洒的鲜血
然而还有人在质疑上帝的愤怒是否真实
我们龌龊的政府竟然纵容肛交[同性恋]
离婚、堕胎
还有人觉得,这不是反基督的人所犯下的罪恶
你是犹太人也好,黑人也好,妓女也好
即便是个废话连篇喜欢进化论的无神论者也好
振奋人心的演说,你看到瓦伦丁在哪了吗
朋友们,虽然祂是个公正的神
但祂也无力回天了...
美国必将灭亡
你确定我们这距离安全
我们离他们1000英尺远,怎么了
万一计算错误怎么办
你只需要相信我就是了
犹太人,黑人,同性恋
魔鬼将永生永世焚烧着他们
不好意思
你要去哪,嘿,你怎么回事啊
我是个天主教男妓
最近和一个黑人犹太教男友享受婚外性行为
他在军方的堕胎诊所工作
所以撒旦万岁,祝你周末愉快,夫人
该死,他要走了,我现在就要开始测试了
希望这帮怪胎都有我们的电话卡
我叫你坐下
像你这种异教徒就该滚出去
就好像恶魔现在真会拯救你似的
你会吃了自己的孩子,你会被主的鲜血溺死
他不会拯救你的
我操
我看不下去了,你赶紧过来
天啊,我操
加拉哈德,听到我说话吗,哈利
哈利,你到底怎么回事
把音量调小点声好吗
- 没想到效果这么好  - 说的是什么样的结果
百分之百
所以每个人都被影响了,不管他们有没有电话卡
而且附加好处是除掉了那个金士曼
还没有
你真该看看这个
你对我做了什么,我完全控制不了自己
我杀光了所有人
- 而且是我想这么做  - 这方法不赖吧
简单来说,就是神经波刺激了攻击行为的核心区域
同时关闭了其抑制作用
电波是通过你那肮脏的免费电话卡传播的
我猜的没错吧
你知道这样看起来像什么吗
像我俩都爱看的老电影里的场景
现在我会告诉你我的全部计划
然后我会想出一些稀奇复杂的方式来干掉你
而你也会想出同样复杂的逃生办法
这听起来不错
可惜这不是在拍电影
不
他死了吗
你朝人头上来一枪通常就是这个结果
感觉不错吧
不,一点都不好,太他妈的难受啦
什么,你都杀了教堂里那么多人
这不过是其中一个
没有,他们是互相残杀的
好吧,把倒计时设好,明天开始狂欢
美国必将灭亡
亚瑟
- 你看到了吗  - 看到了,很难过
召集金士曼
你看不出来我至今所做的一切都是为了补偿他吗
我看见了一个有潜力的年轻人
他可以完成使命而且想有所作为
金士曼
亚瑟,哈利死了
加拉哈德死了
因此,我们刚为他举杯致敬
那你肯定知道那个变态的阴谋
这个世界有多少人有那张电话卡
瓦伦丁可以发个信号给他们任何一个人,所有人
如果他们同时回家,那么...
的确,但多亏有了加拉哈德的录音资料
我们有瓦伦丁的供述
这份情报已经移交给相关部门了
我们的工作完成了
这亦是我们逝去的朋友的最崇高的遗赠了
就这样
过来坐下,小伙子
这是1815年拿破仑时期的白兰地
我们只在金士曼特工牺牲时才会喝
加拉哈德非常喜欢你
此时此景,我觉得稍微...
改下规矩也无妨
他们都是金士曼
没错,我们的创始成员
我想你也来一起举杯
敬加拉哈德
哈利说你不喜欢经常破坏规矩
现在又是为何
你很棒,艾格西
或许我会任命你顶替加拉哈德的位置
如果我们在某些政治问题上能达成一致的话
你猜这是什么
不必了,哈利给我展示过,你一点,我就死
我觉得这白兰地喝起来有点恶心
不错嘛
瓦伦丁说服了你,某种意义上
他一解释,我就明白了
当你感染上病毒,你就会发烧
这是人体提高自己的体温来杀死病毒
地球也是这样的,温室效应就是发烧
人类就是病毒,我们让我们的星球病了
优胜劣汰是唯一的希望
如果我们不减少人口,就只有两种后果
宿主杀了病毒,或者,病毒杀了宿主
- 两者之一...  - 结果都一样
病毒都会死
于是瓦伦丁打算自己解决人口问题
如果我们不采取措施,大自然也会
有时优胜劣汰是确保物种生存的唯一办法
历史将见证瓦伦丁作为救世主
是如何拯救人类免遭灭绝
所以是由他来决定谁被淘汰,是吗
他所有富有的合作伙伴都能生存下来
然后他觉得谁有利用价值,他就会保他们平安
- 不管他们是否认同他  - 而你,艾格西
以哈利之名,我诚邀你成为新世界的一员
你是时候该作出抉择了
我宁愿随哈利而去,谢谢
如你所愿
我们这些普通人的通病是,眼疾手快
金士曼教了我不少东西,但手快这一项...
没错,他们是我们的创始成员
我早就学会了
你这个下贱的混蛋
瓦伦丁节倒计时
至安全区或飞往北纬66°58'30 东经61°43'04.8
好了,兰斯洛特,把枪放下,已经确认过了
亚瑟的手机刚刚收到一个新信息
说是要去安全区
我们没有多少时间了
- 你要怎么办  - 问题应该是我们要怎么办
天知道瓦伦丁的名单里有谁
我们别无选择
我们得亲自去解决这事情
跟我来
- 这他们什么玩意  - 我也不知道
你手里拿着的
是单人跨大气运载器
是里根的星球大战计划里衍生的产物
功能简单,但还是能用得上
我们要把瓦伦丁的一颗卫星毁掉
打破卫星链,中止信号
这会让他花上好几小时个来重置
也给我们争取了足够的时间
可以让我黑进瓦伦丁的主机里
然后关闭系统
兰斯洛特,你要使用这玩意,去把你的光环服穿上
瑞典空军
瑞典首相请求降落许可
允许降落
- 给  - 谢谢
- 多少人要来  - 不多,大部分人都自备燃料
我估计我们从没这么紧张过
欢迎您,首相先生
看来植入物可以发射某种抗干扰信号
保证佩戴者不受电话卡的信号波影响
就是这个信号波把所有人
都变成了变态杀人狂
没错,但他们不知道的是
他可以控制植入物
达到超高温从而烧了他们的软组织
瓦伦丁已经选了几个人选作为倒计时警告
他得确保不会炸错人
那现在这玩意能帮我们干嘛
它帮不了,洛克希,我们走
你飞得越高,气球膨胀得越厉害
当你飞到大气层边缘,气球就会爆炸
你必须在那之前将导弹发射出去,知道吗
大气层边缘
一旦你发射完导弹,你必须要解除装备快速降落
祝你好运
你能做到的,好吗
艾格西,快过来,我们没时间了
你要拿亚瑟的邀请函混进去
- 我来假扮亚瑟吗  - 他的邀请函在他手机里
把这个交给他们,用他的真实姓名,切斯特·金
- 那你呢  - 我是飞行员,我得留在这里
- 我穿得了吗  - 这是为你量身定做的
感谢哈利吧,他给你定做的,穿上吧
这些人都他妈怎么了
不知道,大概跟种族大屠杀有关吧
给我话筒
哈喽
都给我听好了
你们这些人都他妈怎么回事
我想提醒各位,今天是值得庆祝的一天
我们不要谈论死亡,而要关注诞生
新时代的诞生
我们不必哀悼那些今天失去生命的人
我们要为他们的牺牲感到荣耀
她有我的电话号码可以回电给我....
因为他们扮演着拯救人类的角色
我们不应该质疑和内疚
你们是被选中的人
在给孩子们讲述的诺亚方舟故事里,诺亚是坏人吗
上帝是坏人吗
还有成双上方舟的动物们呢
绝对不是
没错,就是这样,让我们一起转换心情
尽情吃喝玩乐吧
让我们相约在新时代
洛克希,是我,上面风景如何
- 难看死了  - 我这可是相当不错
- 他们给你定做西装了吗  - 没,还没有
那你要好好期待一下了
我们要去瓦伦丁的基地了,准备出发了
祝你好运
这身打扮很不错,艾格西
感觉也不错,梅林
我是N247驾驶员,查理·基洛,请求降落
允许降落
我操
已侦测到敌方
艾格西,开始行动
切斯特·金
金先生,欢迎
我肯定您遵守了瓦伦丁先生的严格规定
没有携带武器
- 但是您不反对的话...  - 当然
您有其他行李吗
祝贺你,麦克罗夫,你从飞行员晋升为我的贴身男仆了
- 你个混蛋  - 明白了吗,很好
谢谢
艾格西,找个手提电脑,连上网,时间紧迫
记住要自然地混进去
先生,您要点什么喝的吗
马汀尼,搭配杜松子酒,不要伏特加
搅拌十秒,再加少许没开瓶的味美思酒,谢谢
- 梅林,开始记录了么  - 是的,集中注意力
兰斯洛特,你做得很好,就快到了
好的,梅林
艾格西,快点帮我连上网
好的,马上来
兰斯洛特,你快接近海拔极限了
那些气球气球撑不了多久了
准备发射导弹
旧社会已死,新社会万岁
非常赞同
我是莫顿·林德斯特
我是切斯特·金,你怎么连上网的,我不...
哦,这是个封闭式网络,你看,仅授权可用
我已经锁定卫星
你知道正确的时间吗,我想我的表还在之前的时区
哦,好的,我看看
选择模式
系统分析中
- 艾格西,连上了,快滚回来飞机里  - 这就来
兰斯洛特,祝你好运,发射倒数,三,二...
别激动
你他妈的在这干嘛
很明显,我的家族受邀前来了
你他妈给我站起来,慢慢来
该死,兰斯洛特,快点发射,另一个气球要爆了
好的,梅林,我快好了,再给我点时间
瓦伦丁,我抓到了一个间谍
V镜,放大
我操,是那个年轻男仆
狗娘养的
好了
哦,糟糕,拉响警报
我不想有什么差池
好了,你发出两分钟警报,我开始重写系统
开始倒计时
启动飞机升降器
- 你看到他吗  - 在这儿
艾格西,左转,前方有两名警卫
兰斯洛特,解除装备,快
艾格西,一直向前然后右转,那还有两个
好的,每个人站起来,V日倒计时
欢迎来到新的时代
螺旋形下降中
艾格西,左转有个小的隧道
我们开始吧
十
九
八
七
六
五
四
三、二、一
生物识别成功
系统故障
很好,你们俩都做的很好
这不行了
本来可以的,他妈的怎么回事
干的漂亮,洛克希,好姑娘
我们损失了一个卫星
系统分析完成
不,不,我没有任何办法避开这个黑进系统
已侦测到生物识别安全系统检测
怎么了,有什么问题吗
拜托,不用拿枪吧,我只是个飞行员
操,梅林
快上来
快点
- 他妈的快点离开这吧  - 不行
我进不去瓦伦丁的主机,它有生物识别安全系统
你得回去那地方,确保他的手不能碰到操作台
- 你他妈的在开玩笑吗  - 恐怕不是
那给我枪
这是我的,我给你看看你的吧
选得好
重新形成卫星链要多久
大概是一到两个小时
胡说,把这两个靠一起的连起来不就可以了
但是那个不是你的
V镜,打给E
E,我是V,听着兄弟,我最后关头出了点问题
我需要帮助
我的一个卫星损毁了
它旁边刚好有一个你的卫星
你真懂我,要多久才能完成
走
马上就能连接上
瓦伦丁要用别人的卫星
用不了多久他就要重新连接上形成卫星链
已进行到20%了
艾格西,瓦伦丁给你准备了一份大礼,赶紧行动
那个金士曼死了没
还没有,不过也快了
很好
梅林,我死定了
我也一样
两边都有人围攻,我没有退路了
洛克希,帮我一个忙
给我妈打个电话
告诉她把自己和迪恩还有宝宝分开锁好门
还有告诉她,我爱她
我操,完蛋了
梅林,还记得你说的那些对我们毫无帮助的植入物吗
你能把它们全部激活吗
好了,这下轮到我了,瓦伦丁
噢,不好,他在搞什么鬼
我中止不了程序
是否激活安全植入物
是的,激活吧
安全植入激活
不要
我的老天
真他妈壮观啊
梅林,你他妈的真是天才
他妈的外面出什么事了
你不是那个失踪的公主吗
你能把我弄出去吗
要是能的话,你会给我一个吻吗
我一直梦想着能亲吻公主
要是你现在把我弄出去,我不单止会给你一个吻
你妈逼
你真以为我会蠢得给自己植入个芯片吗
你他妈的是疯子吗
那些无辜的人是为什么自杀的
你屁都没能阻止
好的,我锁好了门,现在我要做什么
照我说的,把你的女儿放进卫生间,然后丢掉钥匙
还在继续呢
- 你他妈的疯了  - 照着做就好了
艾格西,信号开始了
快把瓦伦丁的手从那鬼桌子上挪开
对不起了,亲爱的,我得去拯救世界
如果你拯救了世界,你要不要菊花来一炮
我马上回来
祝你好运
伦敦
里约
趴下
你成功了
这个玻璃坚持不了多久
你待在这里
梅林,快点,我怎么上去
继续射击,我正在找路
明白
我操
我们恢复了
恢复了
太棒了
艾格西,把他那该死的手挪开
狠狠地教训他,亲爱的
首尔,加拉加斯,孟买
他妈的杀啊,杀光你们的朋友吧
艾格西,世界要他妈完蛋了
- 他死了没  - 还没
别玩儿了,快杀了他
葛希尔,葛希尔
快点
杀了他
干的漂亮
好样的,太棒了,艾格西
干的漂亮,艾格西,你也很棒,兰斯洛特
对不起,妈妈绝不会伤害你的
妈妈绝不会伤害你的,对不起
还好吗
哈利会为你骄傲的,艾格西
他是对的
怎么样啊,哥们
这时候你要对我说什么电影名言了吗
跟你和哈利说的一样
可惜我们不是在拍电影,伙计
很好
艾格西,你去哪,不用拿香槟,飞机上有很多
- 你拯救世界了吗  - 没错,我拯救世界了
- 要进来吗  - 是的
梅林,门锁住了,怎么进去
26、25
梅林,你真棒
艾格西,欠我人情啊
艾格西
我的天哪
后面还有,别走开!
米歇尔,关掉那个鬼东西,它搞到我很烦躁
我倒是喜欢这首歌
开着吧,妈妈
小瘪三回来了
你终于要回来和谈了吗,小子
还是你又要逃跑,瞧你穿的这副人模狗样的
你说西装吗
不
我认识的一个朋友带我去了
萨维尔路上的一家裁缝店
他给了我一份工作,妈妈
还有许多额外福利
包括一栋房子
过来和我一起住吧,妈妈
- 来吧  - 你给我坐下
你妈等一下就会到医院探望你了,听到了吗
别理他,艾格西,走吧,快点走
好吧
对,乖乖听你妈的话
你别以为找个裁缝就以为这破衣服会适合你
你个烂货
我的一个好朋友说过
不知礼
无以
立也
- 迪恩  - 你他妈闭嘴
艾格西,我他妈的来教你什么叫做礼仪...
那么
我们是要这样傻站一整天,还是要来痛快打一架
谨以此片纪念我的母亲凯茜
她总能在平凡中彰显不凡
是她教会了我如何做好一个金牌绅士